<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
     xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
     xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
     xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
     xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
     xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
    >

    <channel>
        <title>Newsroom | Lightspeed POS</title>
        <atom:link href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/feed/?post_type=news" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com</link>
        <description></description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 11:20:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <sy:updatePeriod>
            hourly        </sy:updatePeriod>
        <sy:updateFrequency>
            1        </sy:updateFrequency>
        
            <item>
                <title>Lightspeed to acquire Ecwid and NuORDER to unify commerce ecosystem and ignite business creation</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/ecwid-nuorder-acquisition/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/ecwid-nuorder-acquisition/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 11:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amber van Moessner]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Acquisitions accelerate Lightspeed’s transformation to complete commerce platform for businesses throughout the world Lightspeed (TSX: LSPD) (NYSE: LSPD), the one-stop commerce platform for merchants around the world to simplify, scale [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/b91d8443-ma_blog_1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="Lightspeed acquires ecwid and nuORDER" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/b91d8443-ma_blog_1.jpg" /><p style="text-align: center;"><strong><em>Acquisitions accelerate Lightspeed’s transformation to complete commerce platform for businesses throughout the world</em></strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (TSX: LSPD) (NYSE: LSPD), the one-stop commerce platform for merchants around the world to simplify, scale and create exceptional customer experiences, today announced it has entered into definitive agreements to acquire two global leaders in digital commerce. Once closed, the acquisitions will provide Lightspeed customers new entry points to the digital economy, unprecedented supply chain management as well as increased opportunities to provide outstanding customer experiences online. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the past year, commerce has fundamentally transformed for the businesses that make up the backbone of the global economy. New businesses need fast and easy ways to sell online, while established merchants plan to invest even more in the tools and experiences that will unite their digital and physical operations. Lightspeed will acquire </span><a href="https://www.ecwid.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ecwid</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, a US-based best-in-class global eCommerce platform, that allows customers to create standalone businesses in minutes. Once integrated, the combination of Lightspeed and Ecwid will help merchants reach shoppers where they are, whether on social media or digital marketplaces, ushering in newfound selling flexibility and omnichannel experiences. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition, following the strong initial reception and success of the </span><a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/partners/supplier-network/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Supplier Network</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, Lightspeed has announced it has entered into a definitive agreement to acquire </span><a href="https://www.nuorder.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">NuORDER</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, a transformative digital platform connecting businesses and suppliers. Together, Lightspeed and NuORDER will create an industry-leading bridge between the merchant and supplier experience, simplifying product ordering for retailers and offering brands crucial insight into how their products move. The acquisition will capitalize on the early success of the Lightspeed Supplier Network and accelerate the growth of Lightspeed’s financial services offerings, including </span><a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/pos/retail/payments/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Payments</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and Lightspeed Capital, while establishing the company as a global distribution network for leading brands, such as Canada Goose, Converse and Arc’teryx.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“By joining forces with Ecwid and NuORDER, Lightspeed becomes the common thread uniting merchants, suppliers and consumers, a transformation we believe will enable innovative retailers to adapt to the new world of commerce,” said Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO of Lightspeed. “As economies reopen and business creation accelerates, we hope to embolden entrepreneurs with the tools they need to simplify their operations and scale their ambitions.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To learn more, <a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2021/Lightspeed-to-acquire-Ecwid-and-NuORDER-to-unify-commerce-ecosystem-and-ignite-business-creation/default.aspx">read our official press release</a>. </span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/b91d8443-ma_blog_1.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/b91d8443-ma_blog_1.jpg</image><author>Amber van Moessner</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed and OpenTable partner in UK to aid ‘roaring comeback’ to restaurant dining</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-and-opentable-partner-in-uk-restaurant-dining/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-and-opentable-partner-in-uk-restaurant-dining/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 12:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amber van Moessner]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Announcement comes on the heels of Lightspeed’s Order Anywhere launch in Europe and the UK Lightspeed, the one-stop commerce platform for merchants around the world to simplify, scale and provide [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="994" height="468" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/1eaf9e44-open_table_pr_image_9x16-4.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="Lightspeed and OpenTable partner in UK to aid ‘roaring comeback’ to restaurant dining" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/1eaf9e44-open_table_pr_image_9x16-4.jpg" /><p style="text-align: center;"><strong><em>Announcement comes on the heels of Lightspeed’s Order Anywhere launch in Europe and the UK<br />
</em></strong></p>
<p>Lightspeed, the one-stop commerce platform for merchants around the world to simplify, scale and provide exceptional customer experiences, has today announced a partnership with one of the world’s leading providers of online restaurant reservations, OpenTable. The partnership will see a rich integration between Lightspeed and OpenTable, furnishing restaurants with a suite of tools to streamline service and boost efficiency as they look to recover from the pandemic and provide a safe dining experience as lockdown lifts.</p>
<p><a href="https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/uk-economy-reopening-covid-19-data-gdp-spending-deutsche-bank-barclays-pantheon-macroeconomics-130719351.html?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly9maW5hbmNlLnlhaG9vLmNvbS9uZXdzL3VrLXByZWxpbWluYXJ5LXBtaS1hcHJpbC1paHMtbWFya2l0LXJlb3BlbmluZy1sb2NrZG93bi1jb3ZpZC0xOS1jb3JvbmF2aXJ1cy0wODM2MjExNDQuaHRtbA&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAGBIxvc3NFTjx0D328yHaJA9ju5fuyR0fZzWU56kMGWwaUBWd_OL3QeEmOuwH0Mnslr_uAOerB2yZIbZlNX-EZVmZ34ZD7VgGW2x0xbQXFVZxgrI89bu4hT-Rx165qhvseAmkxrDOySlCq86gfKX9CHYz6-tKQ8MhgOatxMHN4Vl">Data from Deutsche Bank</a> and OpenTable suggests the United Kingdom is currently making a &#8220;roaring comeback&#8221; across all sectors, including the restaurant trade. <a href="https://www.opentable.com/state-of-industry">According to OpenTable data</a>, numbers for seated diners are up on average 42% between the 17th and 23rd of May versus the same days in 2019, as diners return to indoor spaces. As pubs, restaurants, and other hospitality venues reopen their doors to indoor dining, having a powerful reservation solution is critical to managing restaurant capacity, keeping track of guests, and ensuring they adhere to COVID19 safety measures.</p>
<p>“This partnership gives management and staff the ability to provide a VIP experience with every reservation with guest details at their fingertips,” said Adrian Valeriano, Managing Director of EMEA, Lightspeed. “OpenTable is the industry leader in the online and mobile reservation space and Lightspeed powers the businesses that are the backbone of the global economy. We’re proud to bring more resources like this, and <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.co.uk/blog/lightspeed-order-anywhere/">Order Anywhere</a>, to our customers in the United Kingdom to help them elevate hospitality and maintain safety with every reservation.”</p>
<p>In early April, <a href="https://www.opentable.com/state-of-industry">OpenTable restaurant bookings were approaching pre-COVID levels</a> (down by only 21% compared to 2019). In Manchester, the seated diner data told an even more encouraging story, as reservations were up 53% from 2019.</p>
<p>As the UK hospitality industry anticipates a busy few months ahead, the partnership between OpenTable and Lightspeed will provide restaurants with timely, unique benefits, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Increase table turnaround with up-to-the-second table status, so hosts know the progress of every table in real-time down to the course being experienced.</li>
<li>Turn tables faster and streamline service with automated check creation for every seated reservation.</li>
<li>New guests created in OpenTable are synced to Lightspeed, creating new customer profiles and giving managers deeper insights to better understand their customer base.</li>
<li>Check data from Lightspeed pulls into OpenTable, so that a restaurant can quickly learn more about their guests&#8217; favorite menu items and provide more personalized service.</li>
</ul>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Order Anywhere Delivers on the New Era of Hospitality</span></h2>
<p>With global adoption of takeout and meal delivery, hospitality businesses are looking for solutions to manage and streamline takeout and delivery services. <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.co.uk/blog/lightspeed-order-anywhere/">Lightspeed’s Order Anywhere</a> is the latest addition to their innovative product suite for the hospitality industry, now available in the United Kingdom, France, and Switzerland. For restaurateurs, Order Anywhere brings all dine-in, takeaway, and online orders together in one dashboard, eliminating the need for expensive marketplace solutions, and allowing contact-free ordering, dining, and payment – anywhere, any time, using any device.</p>
<p><strong>Order Anywhere enhances Lightspeed&#8217;s hospitality commerce platform into a powerful digital hub where restaurateurs can simplify and easily scale their businesses:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Seamless integration and real-time updates: Accept online orders directly from the Lightspeed system, managing your online, take out and table service orders all in a single location. Send email updates to guests so that they are informed of the status of their order from start to finish.</li>
<li>Effortless and contactless ordering: Offer your guests a wide range of secure and flexible collection and dine-in options, including the ability to order and pay via a QR code at the table, or place an order online for now or later. All this without paying any commission to third parties.</li>
<li>Streamlined Online Experience: Lightspeed Order Anywhere gives users the ability to personalize and customize their website information such as opening hours, cooking times, and pick-up options.</li>
<li>Offer an accessible and feature-rich Digital Menu, including multi-lingual item descriptions and allergen notifications, with accurately described dishes to captivate your guests and increase check size on each order.</li>
</ul>
<p>For businesses looking to grow, adapt, or become more efficient, Order Anywhere empowers restaurants to offer a personalized, flexible omnichannel experience. Both Order Anywhere and the OpenTable integration are must-have tools for the busy summer ahead in hospitality.</p>
<p>To learn more about the <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.co.uk/integrations/opentable/">OpenTable partnership, click here</a>. To learn more about <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.co.uk/blog/lightspeed-order-anywhere/">Order Anywhere, visit our blog.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/1eaf9e44-open_table_pr_image_9x16-4.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/1eaf9e44-open_table_pr_image_9x16-4.jpg</image><author>Amber van Moessner</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed teams up with Google to help retailers increase local shopping revenue</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-teams-up-with-google-to-help-retailers-increase-local-shopping-revenue/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-teams-up-with-google-to-help-retailers-increase-local-shopping-revenue/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 12:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amber van Moessner]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Integration allows omnichannel retailers to automate ads and real-time inventory levels directly from the Lightspeed platform Lightspeed (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel commerce platforms, today [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1536" height="864" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2cda7983-1920x1080_e.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/2cda7983-1920x1080_e.jpg" /><p style="text-align: center;"><strong><em>Integration allows omnichannel retailers to automate ads and real-time inventory levels directly from the Lightspeed platform</em></strong></p>
<p>Lightspeed (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel commerce platforms, today announced a global integration with Google. As small and medium-sized businesses seek to capitalize on current and future economic reopenings and consumer preference to shop locally, Lightspeed has released a comprehensive retail integration that will allow independent retailers to manage their online presence and display accurate inventory levels to local shoppers directly from their Lightspeed commerce platform at no additional cost.</p>
<p>This announcement comes as new data from Google suggests consumers are interested in shopping local, and start their journey with an online search. <strong>Searches for “local” + “business(es)” have grown by more than 80% year over year, including searches like “local businesses near me” and “support local businesses.” Searches for “who has” + “in stock” have grown by more than 8,000% year over year</strong>, including searches like “who has gym equipment in stock.”</p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">The New Google + Lightspeed Integration</span></h2>
<p>The global collaboration between Lightspeed and Google integrates three crucial tools directly into the Lightspeed platform: Google Local Inventory Ads, Google Smart Shopping Campaigns, and Google My Business. This complete integration is vital for omnichannel retailers, who use a multichannel approach to provide a seamless customer experience online or in a physical store. The new Google integration includes:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Google Local Inventory Ads</strong>: Reach local customers with local inventory ads, from directly within the Lightspeed platform. These ads help nearby shoppers know what you have in stock, driving more visits to your physical shop.</li>
<li><strong>Google Smart Shopping Campaigns</strong>: Today&#8217;s consumers are shopping across platforms and devices, online and offline, seamlessly. With Smart Shopping campaigns, products are eligible to show up across all of Google&#8217;s properties and reach users wherever, and whenever, they&#8217;re searching or consuming content.</li>
<li><strong>Google My Business</strong>: Lightspeed customers can get and manage a professional Google My Business listing straight from Lightspeed’s commerce platform. Keep customers up to date with your latest information, whether it’s store hours or COVID-19 safety protocols in place.</li>
</ul>
<p>“We know that so much of business today starts with a Google search,” said Lightspeed CEO Dax Dasilva, “By combining forces, Lightspeed and Google are eliminating the pain points that prevent SMBs from effectively promoting their products online to the communities who prefer to shop local, providing them a springboard to simplify and scale their businesses as they prepare for the welcomed return of in-store shopping.”</p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fueling the “Shop Local” movement</span></h2>
<p>Enabling access to these digital tools directly within the Lightspeed platform is strategically aligned with Lightspeed’s mission to simplify entrepreneurship and level the playing field for independent merchants. The integration, when combined with the Lightspeed Supplier Network, creates a seamless path for local retailers to scale their omnichannel businesses.</p>
<p>“Small and medium-sized businesses have been hit the hardest during the pandemic, but globally we’ve seen a rallying cry to support them,&#8221; says Sabrina Geremia, VP &amp; Country Director, Google Canada. &#8220;Customers are shopping both online and in-store and expect a seamless shopping experience between both. As we look towards recovery, this integration with Lightspeed will provide a scalable solution for Lightspeed merchants of all sizes looking to reach customers in this new omnichannel reality&#8221;</p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Case Study: Customers see a 54% increase in revenue after one month</span></h2>
<p>Three years ago, JP Scholten opened the <a href="https://www.octopodes.nl/">OCTOPODES dive shop</a> with his girlfriend who ran a SCUBA school. After seeing their diving students loaded up with unnecessary gear from other stores, they decided to open a one-stop-shop for the school, and got up and running with Lightspeed Retail and eCommerce.</p>
<p>Scholten quickly jumped at an opportunity to test the new Google partnership. “It was so easy, with three clicks I set our local radius, and that was it. In 24 hours we were everywhere,” Scholten told Lightspeed. “It’s amazing to see it now in our orders as well.”</p>
<p>For OCTOPODES, the new Lightspeed Google integration resulted in an immediate uptick in online orders for specialty items they carry. <strong>“In the first month, our traffic went up 24%, we increased new visitors 48%, and average transaction revenue was up 54%.”</strong> While business is growing, Lightspeed is simplifying Scholten’s day-to-day. “It removes the struggle,” he said. “Now I see my Google campaigns in the Lightspeed platform where I am every day, just one click away. You don&#8217;t have to think about it, Lightspeed does it for you.”</p>
<p><a href="https://www.lifeofthepartystore.com/">Life of the Party</a> in Fort Collins, Colorado, has been serving up costumes, wigs, and makeup for almost 40 years. Brandon Lilly and his wife purchased the store in 2018 and began upgrading their technology. “We chose Lightspeed because we wanted to be able to grow, to utilize both desktop and mobile, have good, strong reporting, and really good inventory management,” said Lilly.</p>
<p>Lilly was an early tester for the Google integration and it has already saved him time and driven new customers to his store. “Having Google’s local inventory ads through our Lightspeed platform is really beneficial in helping reach people that don&#8217;t know about us,” said Lilly. “<strong>That absolutely translates to new customers and drives additional sales.</strong> It&#8217;s a great marketing tool. It drives both new customers and repeat customers, which is what really keeps us in business.”</p>
<p>This new offering from Lightspeed and Google will give retailers increased opportunity to meet consumer needs in 2021, which have fundamentally pivoted to prioritizing shopping local. Google My Business and Local Inventory Ad integrations are currently available to all Lightspeed retail customers. Lightspeed’s Smart Shopping Campaign capability will become available in the coming months.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/lightspeed-teams-up-with-google-to-help-retailers-increase-local-shopping-revenue-301288088.html">For more information, read the official release</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2cda7983-1920x1080_e.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2cda7983-1920x1080_e.jpg</image><author>Amber van Moessner</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Inside Lightspeed podcast: a conversation with Jona Georgiou about the future of Lightspeed Payments</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/inside-lightspeed-the-future-of-lightspeed-payments/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/inside-lightspeed-the-future-of-lightspeed-payments/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 13:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[amy.allen]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Gus Papageorgiou, Head of Investor Relations at Lightspeed, sits down with our General Manager of Payments to talk about Lightspeed’s integrated approach.  As industry disruptors replace traditional payment providers, Lightspeed [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1872" height="979" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/8e770348-11134_visualasset.png" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="Inside Lightspeed podcast: the future of Lightspeed Payments" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/8e770348-11134_visualasset.png" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gus Papageorgiou, Head of Investor Relations at Lightspeed, sits down with our General Manager of Payments to talk about Lightspeed’s integrated approach. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As industry disruptors replace traditional payment providers, Lightspeed Payments is ahead of the curve, delivering the one-stop solution businesses need now. Jona explains what makes our Payments program innovative and how it will play a key role in Lightspeed’s growth.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Download or listen to the entire conversation right here.</span></p>
<audio class="wp-audio-shortcode" id="audio-68886-2" preload="none" style="width: 100%;" controls="controls"><source type="audio/mpeg" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/podcasts/inside_lightspeed/Inside_Lightspeed_Episode_1.mp3?_=2" /><a href="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/podcasts/inside_lightspeed/Inside_Lightspeed_Episode_1.mp3">https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/podcasts/inside_lightspeed/Inside_Lightspeed_Episode_1.mp3</a></audio>
<h2><b>Transcript</b></h2>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Welcome to Inside Lightspeed, the podcast that takes you inside the company powering high performing businesses today. This podcast may include forward looking statements that are based on assumptions and therefore subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from those projected. We undertake no obligation to update these statements except as required by law. You can read about these risks and uncertainties in our filings with U.S. and Canadian securities regulators. Our commentary today may include adjusted financial measures, which are non-IFRS measures. I&#8217;m Gus Papageorgiou, Lightspeed&#8217;s Head of Investor Relations, and today I&#8217;m speaking to Jona Georgiou, Lightspeed&#8217;s general manager of Payments and Financial Services. So let&#8217;s jump right in. Welcome, Jona.</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b>T<span style="font-weight: 400;">hanks, Gus.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Glad to have you here today. So before we get off and start talking about Payments, why don&#8217;t you tell us a little bit about yourself? How long have you been here at Lightspeed?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Oh, I joined Lightspeed a little over two and a half years ago.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Have you spent your entire career in payments? Was payments new to you when you joined Lightspeed?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">No, I&#8217;ve helped a few SaaS </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">(software as a service)</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> companies monetize payments both in North America and globally. But my educational background is in economics. But I&#8217;ve been in the payments field for over 15 years now.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">And you&#8217;re here in Toronto? That&#8217;s right.</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&#8217;s correct.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">All right. So getting into this, I think, Jona, in the last few years, we&#8217;ve seen a lot of software companies integrate payments into their solutions, not only ourselves, but some of our competitors as well. What&#8217;s led to this phenomenon of, you know, payments being integrated with software?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">I&#8217;d say, generally speaking, an all-in-one solution accelerates commerce for SaaS companies. Typically, SaaS companies are focused on enabling their customers to fulfill their business needs effectively. And while enhancing payment has not always been the top priority, eventually accepting payments becomes a challenge that they are trying to solve. Most companies navigate that by referring merchants or their customers to payment processors outside of their ecosystem. But the whole flow of onboarding a customer historically has typically been clunky and neither party has been providing a best-in-class experience for the customer.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">So it really wasn&#8217;t an issue of, there was this big epiphany that, oh, we need to offer Payments. It was kind of, you know, we&#8217;re offering software, payments is a problem, and we need to solve for it. Is that more the way things panned out?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Exactly. One may say that it was a bit of an afterthought because they&#8217;re so focused on offering their core business and making that grow. And the payment space has historically been fragmented. And additionally, with different ways of commerce happening now online, in person, curbside payment has become even a bigger challenge for the SMBs </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">(small and medium-sized businesses)</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and a few legacy payment platforms like FIS, Fiserv saw the benefits they could bring to the SaaS companies by introducing a concept like payment facilitation, where they provide a one-stop-shop experience and additionally add a new revenue stream to SaaS companies.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">And, you know, in the end, I guess the big benefactor here is the customer, because by integrating the Payments into the software, I mean, it just makes life so much easier for our customers. We talk a little bit about that. I mean, how does, you know, instead of going to two different platforms, you know, you have a software running your business and a payments provider, integrating the two, I think it really does in the end help our customers.</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Absolutely. It&#8217;s the complete all-in-one solution that really focuses on merchants and what their needs are and having to give them that single point of contact, a single point of truth for their payments and the POS </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">(point of sale)</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> needs, it takes care of, you know, running the business, the day-to-day of the business, so that the merchant can thrive and focus on their craft.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">It really, I think, in addition, increases accountability, right? Because before you might have the software provider pointing the finger at the payments provider, the payments providers pointing the finger at the software provider. But now by integrating the two, you know, we own the relationship. We own the customer. And so it&#8217;s up to us to make sure that everything works.</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Exactly. And the level of support there is simply more streamlined. Like you said, there&#8217;s no pointing the fingers at one vendor to the other. It&#8217;s really, you secure Payments with a company like Lightspeed and you secure your POS through them as well and your support, and your concerns are addressed by that sole company.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Switching now to kind of the traction of the solution. So, you know, we&#8217;ve said in our last call that about 15% of our U.S. retail GTV </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">(gross transaction value)</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is going through Payments and that took us about 20 months to get there. In Canada, we&#8217;re seeing about 12% of the retail GTV go through Payments and only took us about eight months to get there. You know, what did we learn in the U.S. when we rolled out Payments that allow us to see faster adoption in Canada versus the U.S.? Can we talk about what things we learned and can we apply these as we try to roll this out globally?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yeah. So like any new product, it took a while to get the momentum going when we first launched Payments in the U.S. market. And launching Payments generally requires a lot of due diligence in terms of compliance, card brand rules, regulations. There&#8217;s a risk to think about, risk mitigation, building processes and teams. So we learned so much about the space initially and it was a huge learning curve for us. But most of all, what we learned is about our merchants, their needs. And what we noticed is that this is an underserved market and the customer experience is paramount to Lightspeed, which is why we took our time to get it right. But once we were set up, expansion or the thought of expansion was much easier. Bringing Payments to Canada was simpler because it required, you know, similar rails that we had already built in the U.S. because Canada, too, is credit card heavy. But then there was this element of localized experience that was introduced which is Interac in Canada. And once we understood the localized and understood how to build technology around these localized nuances and choosing the right payment partner, that would give us this opportunity, it became much easier. The adoption and we learn from our go to market strategies and just operations, back office was all streamlined. It put us in a very good position now, when you think about it, when we launch in EMEA </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">(Europe, Middle East and Africa)</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">I want to hit on, you know, regional differences a bit later on. But before we leave North America, you know, we&#8217;ve launched Payments in U.S. hospitality. Obviously, the hospitality industry recently has been struggling due to lockdowns. But, you know, as we kind of hopefully get out of these lockdowns and economies open up, can you talk about our expectations here? You know, especially given the latest two acquisitions of ShopKeep and Upserve that&#8217;s drastically increased our hospitality footprint in North America. You know, as we emerge from these lockdowns, what do you think are the potential for hospitality for us?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">We believe this segment is going to come back strong. I think we are all tired of being home and not socializing and with a large portion of our population getting vaccinated soon, there will be a need for the hospitality industry to be ready and to serve a vast population that has been deprived of basic human behavior, which is socializing and enjoying a meal. For Upserve, this could be huge. They have such a bespoke product to begin with and now with the acquisition, we are in a better position to launch in more markets. ShopKeep, on the other hand, has the vast majority of its customers based in retail and retail fared much better during this period.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">So we&#8217;ve done a pretty good job here in North America and we&#8217;re rolling out hospitality in the U.S. and hopefully Canada is coming soon. But North America is a very important market for us and Canada is our home base. We&#8217;re seeing great growth in places like Australia, which is further along their COVID recovery. And so we have kind of global ambitions for our Payments. And we launched Payments in the UK about a couple of weeks ago. But what&#8217;s next for Lightspeed? Where can we expect our platform to roll out next?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed is a global company. It has been for quite some time. And supporting our customers, not just in North America but globally, is something that we take very seriously. We&#8217;ve learned that providing an all-in-one solution makes our core SaaS products stickier. The long-term value increases tremendously when a merchant attaches Payments to their POS. We are aiming to provide this, you know, unified support across the globe, starting with EMEA and we just launched Lightspeed Payments in the UK, last month. We can see the opportunity here is massive. And building a commerce platform that offers a compelling payment product and incorporates positive customer experiences is huge. It&#8217;s paramount to Lightspeed.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">And, you know, here&#8217;s the one thing I think that people don&#8217;t realize is just how regional Payments is, right? You touched on it earlier, about Interac in Canada. You know, and obviously there are some commonalities globally as the big three card players are pretty much present everywhere. But there&#8217;s still quite a few differences, right? Like I mean, in Germany, I think the bulk of online transactions are not through credit cards, it&#8217;s through the local debit system. And I think the Netherlands is a lot the same. But can you talk about some of these regional challenges that we have to address as we plan to roll this out globally? Maybe give some examples, like if you compare Germany to the U.S., what are kind of the bigger differences between those two countries?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">You&#8217;re absolutely right. The way we pay emerges from culture, habits, innovation, technology that is available to us. And the unique mix of payment methods arises from local circumstances like, you know, government regulations, economic and political conditions, infrastructure, culture, all play a role in what gets offered locally in a region. Different payment methods and preferences are as diverse as people who use them. So, you know, in Germany, for example, adopting digital wallet technologies for e-comm is getting more and more popular. And even with that, it&#8217;s still a cash-based society at the point of sale. This has, of course, changed recently. But from a non-cash perspective, Germany is heavy on debit cards and very low on credit cards. Very, very different from what you see in the U.S., where credit cards are widely used and cash, not so much. And comparing these two countries in the e-comm space, again, U.S. very credit card heavy, whereas Germany, people pay direct debit on e-comm transactions. So you&#8217;ll see these local nuances and the methods of payment changing as you go across the globe. And even in EMEA, every region has its own localized debit and credit and paying methods.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">And of course, it takes time and a lot of programmers to integrate that into our Payments offering.</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Oh, yes, absolutely. I mean, the experience follows a completely different flow from a product standpoint. And also the connectors could be different. Meaning, you know, which terminal is used and which processor is used behind it, could be nuanced based on region as well.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">And I guess the other issue as well is that, you know, traditionally North America has been very retail-oriented for us, for ShopKeep and Upserve, and Europe has been very hospitality oriented. You know, we talk a little bit about that as we roll out our kind of global ambitions for Payments, our global footprint is very much hospitality oriented. How is that going to influence the role of Payments?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The payment experience for retail and hospitality are pretty different. The flows are more complex with hospitality. As an example, the ability to split the bill several ways by customer, it could be by order. And these are more complex flows than purchasing a bike, as an example, from a retail store. Additionally, our merchants (consumers) are different using various services and there are local nuances to consider. We have different squads within Payments, within the Payments team, that look at the consumer experience and they specialize in each vertical. So we have a squad for retail, for hospitality, for golf. But at its core, it&#8217;s still the concept of processing payments. And so companies like Lightspeed look to partner with a global provider that is able to support a business and product needs. We chose to go with Adyen internationally, given their global footprint in the card present space. And once the localization and fiscalization and regulatory frameworks are resolved for each region, we then want to ignite Payments in each region of these geographies for both retail and hospitality</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">You touched on another, I think, important theme here. You know, we did choose Adyen in Europe and Stripe, our partner in North America. What are kind of the benefits for us to kind of maintain multiple partners versus consolidating down to one partner?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">We are a global company, and we serve multiple verticals and there are complexities with that. And no single provider has to this point offered us a solution that meets all of our needs. So certain partners are better suited to certain countries than others, and certain providers offer a better experience depending on whether we are online, in retail, hospitality. And what we’ve really done is designed our system to support multiple processors, and we see a real merit in working with multiple payment partners. </span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">So we’ve talked about hospitality, we’ve talked about retail, and you have to roll out globally, so you&#8217;re going to be very busy over the next few months. Going a little bit beyond that. I mean, one of the initiatives that we rolled out recently as our Supplier Network and everybody internally is pretty excited about the potential there. Still a lot of heavy lifting to get it up to its potential. But, you know, one of the kind of avenues it opens up for us is the potential for B2B </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">(business to business)</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> payments, integrating our suppliers with the merchant or the restaurateur. Can we talk about that? How different is that going to be from what we have currently? What is the potential there? And what do you think are the biggest challenges to making that a reality?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The B2B side of the business, the opportunity is massive, both from an innovation standpoint as well as revenue. The B2B segment has seen some megadeals in the recent years. It adds to the growing list of services you can offer as a company, be it invoicing, you could do international payment processing, payment analytics, issuing cards. The challenge again falls back to the current payment landscape, how they are built. Not all payment companies have an API-first mindset. So to launch Payments in the space successfully, you have to think of all the different payment mediums. One business owner&#8217;s preferred method of payment may not be someone else&#8217;s, and it could be that it&#8217;s not likely supported. So there are these traditional methods of wire transfer. Signing a check, that is pretty prevalent in B2B. Collections is another factor. But moving to a new and modern solution like ours would mitigate potential risks. Lastly, B2B payments is complicated. Coordinating that many payment methods is a time consuming and resource-intensive avenue. And we have to be very strategic on how we bring this to market. There is definitely a potential for additional revenue source here. So at the same time, it provides the consumer the benefits from faster payment, better customer experience, reclaim time, improved operational efficiency and a whole lot more.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of the questions I get a lot from investors is, you know, why isn&#8217;t Payments adoption 100%? Let&#8217;s let&#8217;s talk about that for a bit. You know, first of all, I think there are some industries where we cannot offer Payments currently. Is that correct?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&#8217;s right. The space is heavily regulated. We are not able to sell to a whole list of prohibited merchants. Like I mentioned, CBD, you know, pharmaceuticals and nutraceuticals being one of those. And while this certainly isn&#8217;t the majority of our business, these are industries that we currently support in our core business for retail. This prevents us from getting that 100% adoption you spoke about earlier. Plus with Payments comes risk, right? So we have to be mindful about who we are boarding. We have to make sure we know the merchants, know their customers, know their business requirements. So if a merchant is not able to meet certain risk criteria, we do not board them on Payments.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Do you think eventually we will try to find partners that will help us onboard these merchants, or are we just going to kind of say, okay, well, we can&#8217;t access these merchants, we&#8217;ll just let it go?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">That would be ideal that we support these verticals as well. The standards are changing, specifically for CBD, we hear it in the news. The government, regulatory agencies, banks, financial institutions are evolving their policies around it and becoming more and more accepting. So our hope is that we would be able to support, and we don&#8217;t have to scout for a new high-risk processor and we can leverage our existing partnerships sometime in the future.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hopefully that will just kind of work itself out as some of these regulations change. But okay, so if we remove that fact that, you know, certain segments, certain verticals are not eligible for Payments, aside from that, what is the biggest reason customers decline Payments?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">I think it&#8217;s just oftentimes, it&#8217;s just having to switch. A large portion of our business is in the brick and mortar space and to switch terminals, pay for them, negotiate again, some merchants just don&#8217;t want to go through that, especially if they have an existing deal that is very cost effective. So not all merchants are looking for innovations, especially the really small businesses. They just want to take payments and get paid.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">You have enough issues on your plate when you&#8217;re trying to run a small business. But one of the things I think that helps Payments adoption is just really the value proposition for customers, right? The ability for us to integrate Payments into the software, I think offers a lot more value for our customers. And maybe we could just discuss that for a bit. I mean, if you look at the value proposition, how do we sell this to customers?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are numerous advantages of Lightspeed Payments as an integrated solution. First of all, like I mentioned, it&#8217;s an all-in-one solution that helps the merchant grow and reinvent their business. And they don&#8217;t have to, you know, manage these different relationships with their vendors like the POS and the processor and the accounting and, you know, reconciliation. And merchants are able to process sales faster with integrated payments and with Lightspeed Payments. And, you know, when you process sales faster there&#8217;s less human errors, you don&#8217;t have to punch numbers on your terminal anymore. So, you know, the checkout flows, and becomes more delightful. And, you know, it&#8217;s also automatically syncing your payment information with your sale information. And additionally, it kind of covers all the processing needs, like the whole omni experience online, in store and now curbside. So Payments also provides that customer the insights, that comprehensive reporting, to see their transactions and their respective payouts so they don&#8217;t have to spend time reconciling their books. And it provides a very simple, transparent pricing for the merchants. So no hidden costs or setup fees or monthly minimums or getting, you know, fined for early termination as an example. So that&#8217;s simplicity. And with the value prop, it gets the merchant a complete commerce experience without the hassle of maintaining several different books or vendor relationships. And they can really focus on what they do best.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">I think this really is a key value proposition here and kind of in line with our omnichannel strategy that Dax </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">(Founder and CEO of Lightspeed)</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and JP </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">(President of Lightspeed) </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">are really highlighting, right? I mean, the fact that you have one payment method for in-store, curbside, online also really helps, you know, with the data that you have, the analytics, the loyalty. So you can really kind of optimize your business and your operations and really kind of hopefully help them increase their sales and just make life generally more prosperous for them.</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Absolutely. It truly is that, you know, single source of truth and it adds up. Like it ties in the merchant information to run the business on the data and the products. And they&#8217;re able to seriously streamline some of these dated processes that have been used historically.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">So, you know, if you look over the next few months and years as there&#8217;s no shortage of challenges on our hands, on your hands. You have to roll out Payments globally, what you&#8217;re doing. We have to light up both retail and hospitality. So a lot of work there. But as we knock down these obstacles, what do you see as the impediment for us achieving a much higher penetration of our GTV going through Payments? I mean, versus right now, we&#8217;ve said that less than 10% of our GTV is going through Payments if we look out. Do you think there&#8217;s any impediments for us getting that number much, much higher?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are challenges. And part of the challenge is what I mentioned in the beginning of our chat: is a lot of SaaS companies were so focused on their core business that Payments was more on the referrals side. And now part of the challenge has been launching Payments broadly beyond North America is that these several different referral partnerships that we have to look into, they don&#8217;t bring that kind of economics that Payments does. So, yes, a few challenges, but for the most part, these are all solvable. Some might be more complex than others. But no, I see the penetration of GTV growth tremendously in the future.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another question I get is just on the margins of Payments. And we&#8217;ve stated publicly that we&#8217;re getting roughly 2.6% per transaction and our gross margins for Payments is in the mid 20% range. You know, if we look out a few years, hopefully our GTV grows, hopefully our customer base grows. What can we expect from margins from the payment solutions over the long term?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">I think cost optimization plays a role. It&#8217;s something that I have had in my mind for quite some time. There are several ways to handle them. It could be through negotiating better rates with your payment provider, and as we grow our business and have more GTV flowing through Payments, economies of scale kicks in and we get better rates. So then on top of that, if you send level three data, which is, you know, just enhanced transaction data, like adding zip code and tax rate and invoice reference number to your processors, you know, you can qualify for better interchange rate, which makes up the majority of our cost. So bring additional optionality on Payments also to improve these margins, such as instant payout, that could bring additional revenue streams to Payments and financial services overall.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">So it&#8217;s not just scale and cost. It&#8217;s also, you know, offering more financial services. And just so that hits on my next point before I let you go, I think Lightspeed Capital also falls within your responsibilities. Now we have our Capital offering, and we recently acquired ShopKeep which had a much more advanced Capital business. Can you discuss the difference between these approaches, between Lightspeed and ShopKeep? </span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Both capital products are merchant cash advances. Lightspeed Capital is still pretty much in its early stage and we are building on some flows within the product. ShopKeep Capital, on the other hand, has been around since 2019. So prior to the acquisition of ShopKeep, that product, they were using their own funds and they built the product for both integrated payment customers as well as non-integrated. They built their own underwriting and operations and team and they have their own list of eligibility requirements. And once a merchant&#8217;s passed those eligibility requirements, they&#8217;re able to bring capital to those customers, regardless whether they&#8217;re ShopKeep merchants that are integrated or not. The ex-CFO of ShopKeep is executing on this initiative and exploring ways to expand it further. Lightspeed Capital used Stripe infrastructure to offer capital to only a group of customers that are Lightspeed Payments-only merchants. The eligibility thresholds are a little less flexible because, you know, in that model, Stripe owns the risk at the moment and we are iterating and constantly iterating as we are learning more. But Lightspeed Capital is evolving and as the product is getting built, we are looking at creative ways which strive to improve the experience and grow adoption. But I must point out, the advantage here on Lightspeed Capital is we are learning a ton. We are learning so much about having this offering, what merchants&#8217; needs are, and a lot around the requirements where and how they&#8217;re using the capital. So the good thing is it&#8217;s all under one umbrella now.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">And if you if you look at the offerings that we&#8217;re putting out there and the traction, I mean, obviously still very early. Can you discuss a little bit about the, you know, the typical working capital advance that we&#8217;re seeing and maybe about the duration of the payback?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">We are still early in the process, so we are seeing how it evolves. Our maximum advance is $100,000 USD, but our average is much lower than that. Generally an advance is set to be repaid through daily reimbursements over six to nine months.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">And then if you look at the two, if we compare Lightspeed then versus the ShopKeep approach, you know, which do you think will be more appropriate for us going forward?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&#8217;ll be a blend of the two. Both will be upgraded to the verticals we serve. This is us looking ahead, you know, eight to 10 months in and making this offer global while Lightspeed Capital will operate around the boundaries of Lightspeed Payments. ShopKeep, on the other hand, given they are quite a bit more advanced in their product, will be extended to merchants currently not on Payments but are still looking to get that, you know, aid to run the business. The aim here is to be there for our merchants when they need us, specifically during times like these, right? So where they are looking for support or thinking of ways on how to bring their business back and thrive again in the economy as things open up, we want to be there for our merchants and help them with Capital where possible. And we are looking to be their partner during this phase and looking to support them as much as possible.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">And so, as you say, currently Capital for us is only available in the U.S., but our intentions are eventually to roll this out globally, correct?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">We are looking into it. Obviously, there will be local regulations to follow, just like we had to do for Payments. But we are working through those details at the moment.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ok, one last topic before I let you go here. So we&#8217;ve launched Payments and it&#8217;s doing quite well. More recently, we launched Capital and you know, we think that business has promise as well. What do you think we can offer in addition to these financial services for our customers? If we look out a few years, what is the potential for Lightspeed&#8217;s financial services to expand not just geographically, but in terms of the solutions that we offer?</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Quite honestly, we have a whole flywheel of financial products that would be a natural extension of Payments to build. We have the foundation done, which is Payments, and we are getting better and better at that. And then the idea is to help our merchants make, move and manage their money. So the obvious one here is instant deposit, paying the merchant their sales volume instantly on the debit cards. And that&#8217;s something that would be the next stop for us.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Well, it seems that there&#8217;s no shortage of things on your to-do list over the next few years, so that&#8217;s great. Jona, I want to thank you for joining us today. And we look forward to maybe speaking to you again in the future.</span></p>
<p><b>Jona Georgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thank you, Gus. It was a pleasure. I&#8217;m always happy talking about Payments.</span></p>
<p><b>Gus Papageorgiou: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Great. Thanks, everyone. Thank you for listening to Inside Lightspeed. For more information about Lightspeed&#8217;s integrated payment offering, visit LightspeedHQ.com. If you aren&#8217;t already, be sure to follow Lightspeed on LinkedIn, Facebook, Twitter and Instagram. Our handle is LightspeedHQ. Original music for the episode was composed by Timothy LeClaire. The episode was edited by Jonathan Beaten and produced by Lightspeed. See you next time.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/8e770348-11134_visualasset.png" length="0" type="image/png" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/8e770348-11134_visualasset.png</image><author>amy.allen</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed partners with U.S. Small Business Administration to expedite hospitality industry relief</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-sba-partnership/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-sba-partnership/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 21:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amber van Moessner]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Global commerce leader to provide application assistance to US restaurants as they ramp up for post-vaccine re-openings Lightspeed (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel commerce platforms, [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/9e137cfb-us-sba_1200x628_news.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="Lightspeed SBA Partnership" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/9e137cfb-us-sba_1200x628_news.jpg" /><p style="text-align: center;"><strong><em>Global commerce leader to provide application assistance to US restaurants as they ramp up for post-vaccine re-openings</em></strong></p>
<p>Lightspeed (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel commerce platforms, today announced a partnership with the U.S. Small Business Administration (SBA) to help hospitality merchants access new funds made available through the $28.6 billion Restaurant Revitalization Fund (RRF). This partnership with the SBA will provide Lightspeed hospitality merchants in the United States, independent restaurants hit hard by the global pandemic, an accelerated application process for RRF grant applications.</p>
<p>“Lightspeed is proud to be a partner to the SBA and the Restaurant Revitalization Fund to help independent restaurants access critical funding as we prepare for brighter, better days for our industry,” said Sheryl Hoskins, Lightspeed’s global General Manager of Hospitality. “I’ve worked closely with local governments and chambers of commerce in the United States since COVID-19 hit our customers and we are thrilled to see an increase in support for the independent hospitality businesses that are the backbone of our communities and economy.”</p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Help is Here”</span></h2>
<p>Through May 25, the SBA will prioritize processing and awarding funds to businesses that are majority-owned and controlled by women, veterans, or socially and economically disadvantaged groups.</p>
<p>“We are starting the process to help restaurants and bars across the country devastated by the pandemic, and this is our message: Help is here. With the launch of the Restaurant Revitalization Fund, we’re prioritizing funding to the hardest-hit small businesses – irreplaceable gathering places in our neighborhoods and communities that need a lifeline now to get back on their feet,” <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/rohitarora/2021/04/24/restaurant-revitalization-fund-offers-much-needed-assistance-to-struggling-industry/?sh=141e83a3c450">said SBA Administrator Isabella Casillas Guzman</a>.</p>
<p>By being an SBA partner, Lightspeed customers can easily access sales documentation needed to apply for SBA loans. Lightspeed has continued to roll out new technology since the outbreak of the COVID-19 pandemic to pivot to the demands of the new era of hospitality, streamlining <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-order-ahead/">online and contactless ordering</a>, and <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/new-integrated-payments-north-america/">integrated payments</a> for independent restaurants.</p>
<p>For restaurants that have not applied yet, visit the <a href="https://www.sba.gov/funding-programs/loans/covid-19-relief-options/restaurant-revitalization-fund">SBA site</a> to view <a href="https://www.sba.gov/funding-programs/loans/covid-19-relief-options/restaurant-revitalization-fund#section-header-8">eligibility information</a>, <a href="https://ussbaforgiveness.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/sections/360013076472-Program-Questions">FAQs</a>, and <a href="https://restaurants.sba.gov/requests/borrower/login/?next=/">register an application</a>. The <a href="https://restaurant.org/downloads/pdfs/business/applying-for-rrf">National Restaurant Association has also produced a step-by-step guide</a> to filling out the application.</p>
<p>To learn more, <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/lightspeed-partners-with-us-small-business-administration-to-expedite-hospitality-industry-relief-301283798.html">see the official press release here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/9e137cfb-us-sba_1200x628_news.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/9e137cfb-us-sba_1200x628_news.jpg</image><author>Amber van Moessner</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed launches enhanced integrated accounting tools to save time and streamline tasks for independent business owners</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/integrated-accounting-launch/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/integrated-accounting-launch/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 15:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Meghan O'Neil]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[In a recent poll conducted by OnePoll, Lightspeed found that business owners in the United Kingdom reported spending five to eight hours a week on their business finances, and 66% [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="2000" height="750" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/cb1eb295-lightspeed_accounting_blog-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/cb1eb295-lightspeed_accounting_blog-1.jpg" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a recent poll conducted by OnePoll, Lightspeed found that business owners in the United Kingdom reported spending five to eight hours a week on their business finances, and 66% said they still manually track their books, which can lead to significant reporting errors. Lightspeed (NYSE:LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel commerce platforms, today announced the release of new integrated accounting tools for Lightspeed Accounting that help independent business owners securely automate bookkeeping tasks, saving hours a week by eliminating the need to manually transfer data, connecting their Lightspeed platform directly to their accounting software. </span></p>
<p><b>Simplified Accounting with a Broad Range of Tools</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The direct integration allows business managers to automate sending all their sales data directly to a broad range of accounting softwares like Quickbooks, Xero, Sage, and more. By automating the data transfer, business owners reduce the hours spent on their business finances. Lightspeed Accounting users spend on average five minutes a day on bookkeeping tasks that would previously take hours to complete manually. </span></p>
<p><b>The new Lightspeed accounting integration:</b></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Reduces the likelihood of human errors by automating manual processes</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Provides an automated daily summary of sales</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tracks revenue streams across multiple locations with complete accuracy </span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“No one starts a small retail business or restaurant because they’re passionate about paperwork,” said Lightspeed Founder and CEO Dax Dasilva. “Business owners pride themself on their products and customer service. At Lightspeed, we try to make the complex work easy, so they can focus on the tasks they are passionate about. Using integrated accounting tools, much like </span><a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/pos/retail/payments/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">integrated payments</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, saves time and money for entrepreneurs.”</span></p>
<p><b>A “Nightmare”: Majority of Merchants Still Manually Track Their Books </b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed’s integrated accounting tools have been a game-changer for </span><a href="https://www.facebook.com/virtuosityboston/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Virtuosity Musical Instruments</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, a Boston-based instrument sales, and repair shop. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“With Lightspeed, my books take me five minutes a day and we’re done. It’s really quite simple,” said owner Steve Johnson. “My bookkeeper was very excited to have something that would just drop into Quickbooks on a daily download.” </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The key to simplicity for Johnson is the integration with his Lightspeed platform. “Errors happen when you have to manually input something more than once,” he said of his previous accounting system. “It gives me nightmares when I see people using a spreadsheet for their accounting. Lightspeed Accounting lets the tools work for you.” </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the OnePoll survey, Lightspeed found that:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">78% manage their financials on their own. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">66% are still using manual entry into spreadsheets to track their accounting. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">51% spend 5-8 hours a week just on business finances. (Lightspeed accounting user spends on average 5 minutes a day.)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">33% said they need more support with accounting and tax management, while 42% said they need more overall support with financial management. </span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kamal Chami owns two restaurants in Canada and uses Lightspeed Accounting for both. &#8220;Lightspeed Accounting simply does everything for me,” said Chami. “I get 30 minutes back every morning due to all my information being sent directly to my QuickBooks accounts. With this new automated workflow, I now only have to confirm the data and I can spend the rest of my time on other tasks.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This enhanced integration replaces the existing accounting integration that Lightspeed previously offered to customers in North America and the United Kingdom. The enhanced version of Lightspeed Accounting is a completely new and improved integration and is fully integrated into the Lightspeed platform to improve the customer’s experience. The initial rollout is available immediately to hospitality merchants in the United States and Canada, and will soon expand to the UK, Netherlands, Belgium, France, and Switzerland. For Retail businesses the tools will become available over the summer wherever Lightspeed Retail is sold.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/cb1eb295-lightspeed_accounting_blog-1.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/cb1eb295-lightspeed_accounting_blog-1.jpg</image><author>Meghan O'Neil</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed launches Lightspeed Payments in United Kingdom and Europe in expansion of financial services</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-payments-united-kingdom-europe/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-payments-united-kingdom-europe/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 13:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed brings Lightspeed Payments to UK customers as 94% of UK-based merchants look to integrate payments to simplify and scale their businesses  Lightspeed, a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel commerce [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/6cc6ffa5-lightspeed_payments_media_logo-1200x628-1.png" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/6cc6ffa5-lightspeed_payments_media_logo-1200x628-1.png" /><p style="text-align: center;"><b>Lightspeed brings Lightspeed Payments to UK customers as 94% of UK-based merchants look to integrate payments to simplify and scale their businesses</b><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed, a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel commerce platforms, today announced the initial availability of </span><a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/pos/retail/payments/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Payments</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> for hospitality merchants in the United Kingdom and Europe. Lightspeed’s integrated payments experience gives small and medium-sized businesses in the hospitality industry access to key functionalities made crucial by the global pandemic, including mobile and contactless payments, ahead of anticipated economic reopenings. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Payments will be rolled out to hospitality merchants in the United Kingdom, followed by retail. This will continue for Lightspeed merchants throughout France, Belgium, the Netherlands, Germany, and Switzerland. The United Kingdom is an underserved market when it comes to payments, especially in the hospitality sector, and Lightspeed is thrilled to support these businesses as they begin to re-open for full-capacity dining. </span></p>
<h2><b>94% of UK SMBs See Financial Value of Integrated Payments</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A study Lightspeed conducted with London’s OnePoll and over 300 small business owners found that:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">94% said having integrated POS payments saves money and 79% believe it saves time. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">83% are using mobile payments.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">78% manage their financials on their own. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">34% said they need more support preventing fraudulent payments, while 42% said they need more overall support with financial management. </span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;This is a crucial time for the small and medium-sized businesses we serve and they need simplified solutions that save them time and money,” says Dax Dasilva, founder and CEO of Lightspeed. &#8220;This launch empowers many of our global customers to generate faster, more secure transactions that give them richer data about their business. The United Kingdom has historically seen rapid adoption of new payments solutions and we are excited to add new capabilities and flexibility to the businesses that are the backbone of that economy.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>To integrate with local financial infrastructure, Lightspeed has partnered with the global payments platform Adyen in the United Kingdom and Europe to provide reliable, secure payment processing for customers.</p>
<h2><b>Simplified Payments Provides Relief for SMBs</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Payments proved to be essential for many North American businesses throughout the COVID-19 pandemic. Operating from a single system of record, merchants eliminate the inconvenience of a separate payments provider, gaining a globally-backed, secure platform. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">LeAnna Brun runs </span><a href="https://www.brunmillers.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brunmillers Soapworks</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, a small retail business in Texas. While COVID-19 and recent ice storms wreaked havoc on her tourism-driven business, being able to run her shop online using both Lightspeed eCommerce and Lightspeed Payments has helped keep her business afloat. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Lightspeed has made everything so much easier,” Brun said. “It keeps business moving and having an integrated system is really important. With Lightspeed Payments, I love checking my bank account in the morning. It’s the most painless part of my whole business. Being able to control inventory and payments for online sales and in-store from a single location is extremely valuable. It’s also important to me that my customers feel secure when checking out.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Today&#8217;s announcement furthers Lightspeed&#8217;s commitment to the tens of thousands of customer locations it supports throughout the globe and extends Lightspeed Payments beyond North America, where the company has offered the solution since 2018. </span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2021/Lightspeed-launches-Lightspeed-Payments-in-United-Kingdom-and-Europe-in-expansion-of-tailored-financial-solutions/default.aspx"><span style="font-weight: 400;">To learn more, read our press release here. </span></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/6cc6ffa5-lightspeed_payments_media_logo-1200x628-1.png" length="0" type="image/png" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/6cc6ffa5-lightspeed_payments_media_logo-1200x628-1.png</image><author>Alix Fraser</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed partners with Digital Main Street to help SMBs achieve omnichannel potential</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/partnership-with-digital-main-street/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/partnership-with-digital-main-street/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 13:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Meghan O'Neil]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed has partnered with Digital Main Street (DMS), a programme created by the Toronto Association of Business Improvement Areas (TABIA) with support by the Federal Government of Canada, Province of [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/1390a0e1-dms-partnership-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/1390a0e1-dms-partnership-1.jpg" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed has partnered with Digital Main Street (DMS), a programme created by the Toronto Association of Business Improvement Areas (TABIA) with support by the Federal Government of Canada, Province of Ontario and the City of Toronto.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Through ShopHERE powered by Google, one of the programmes offered by DMS, Lightspeed is helping small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) access its omnichannel platform and help to provide them with the tools they need to thrive. Lightspeed is also committed to supporting the other Digital Main Street programs and support offerings, joining in the mission of helping as many SMBs grow through the adoption of digital tools and technologies as possible.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“At the heart of every thriving community is a healthy main street. Providing businesses with the right digital tools to adapt and succeed is what Lightspeed does.” said Peter Dougherty, Vice-President of Partnerships at Lightspeed. “With DMS, Lightspeed will have a greater opportunity to help SMBs access and benefit from our omnichannel solutions. We remain focused on driving innovation and delivering those democratizing tools, so that we can all come back to a stronger, healthier and more diverse post-pandemic economy.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To be eligible for the ShopHERE program, businesses must be registered in Ontario, and have fewer than 10 full time employees (or fewer than 25 employees if they are a cafe, restaurant, or bar). Additionally, businesses cannot be part of a corporate chain or franchise. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cloud-based, omnichannel capacity was once considered a “nice-to-have feature” but with the global COVID-19 pandemic, it has become a “must-have.” Necessary not just to remain operational but to capitalize on changing consumer behaviour. Lightspeed’s mission for sixteen years has been to future-proof independent businesses by providing them the best in digital platforms and strategies. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“We are thrilled to welcome Lightspeed to our group of partners in support of Digital Main Street.” said John Kiru, Executive Director of the Toronto Association of Business Improvement Areas and founder of DMS. “Now more than ever small business owners across the country need to continue embracing the concept of Digital Transformation not only as part of their recovery but also to thrive in the ever changing consumer landscape. Bringing Lightspeed on board with their focus on omnichannel will be a welcomed addition and support resource for our business community.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Through this partnership Lightspeed and DMS are helping keep SMBs resilient and pushing forward innovation that will future-proof the economy by stimulating economic growth and equipping businesses with the technology to take on any challenge. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“As local economies continue to deal with the impacts of the pandemic, our government is committed to ensuring that our small- and medium-sized enterprises don’t just survive, but thrive,” said the Honourable Mélanie Joly, Minister of Economic Development and Official Languages and Minister responsible for the Federal Economic Development Agency for Southern Ontario. “We are proud to support the partnership between Digital Main Street and Lightspeed and look forward to seeing the impact the platform will have on future proofing small businesses in our communities.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">DMS is proud of doing its part in the coming recovery and helping resilient merchants continue their drive for success.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To read more, please visit <a href="https://digitalmainstreet.ca/lightspeed-dms/">digitalmainstreet.ca/lightspeed-dms</a></span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/1390a0e1-dms-partnership-1.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/1390a0e1-dms-partnership-1.jpg</image><author>Meghan O'Neil</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed to acquire Vend to power global retail expansion</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-to-acquire-vend/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-to-acquire-vend/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 21:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Omnichannel commerce leader grows customer base by more than 20,000 customer locations worldwide, entrenches leadership position in Asia-Pacific MONTREAL, March 11th, 2021 &#8211; Lightspeed POS Inc. (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/d649151a-blog_echo_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/d649151a-blog_echo_1200x628.jpg" /><p style="text-align: center;"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Omnichannel commerce leader grows customer base by more than 20,000 customer locations worldwide, entrenches leadership position in Asia-Pacific</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">MONTREAL, March 11th, 2021 &#8211; Lightspeed POS Inc. (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel commerce platforms, today announced it has entered into a definitive agreement to acquire Vend Limited (Vend), a cloud-based retail management software company. The acquisition strengthens Lightspeed’s global retail base and reinforces the company as a premier omnichannel retail platform worldwide for high-performing small and medium-sized businesses. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The acquisition also builds on Lightspeed’s foothold in Asia-Pacific, approximately doubling the company’s customer base and expanding its retail footprint in that region. The combination of Lightspeed with the talent and technology of Vend, widely acknowledged as providing one of the foremost retail products on the market, will help to further growth by ultimately providing the Vend customer base access to the company’s broader commerce solutions, such as Lightspeed Payments, Lightspeed eCommerce, Lightspeed Loyalty, as well as future access to the Lightspeed Supplier Network. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Subsequent to the closing of the acquisition, Lightspeed will serve as the technology partner of choice for over 135,000 customer locations worldwide as small and medium-sized businesses increasingly turn to the company’s innovative, cloud-based platforms ahead of highly-anticipated economic reopenings in both the retail and hospitality industries. Building on the landmark acquisition of ShopKeep, Lightspeed intends to leverage Vend’s complementary modern technology stack and user experience capabilities to continue to deliver the most advanced commerce capabilities to retailers around the world. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Lightspeed’s mission is to ignite the potential of businesses to enrich the communities they serve, whether they are beloved local neighborhoods or the thriving metropolitan cities we are eager to see bustling with crowds once again,” said Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO of Lightspeed. “We are thrilled to partner with Vend, a team that matches Lightspeed’s passion for retail. That combined drive will position our global retail base of high-performing businesses for success as they emerge from a truly transformational period in the history of modern commerce.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Lightspeed’s global excellence and commitment to community is inspirational to Vend,” says Ana Wight, CEO of Vend. “By joining forces, we will power the global transformation of retail and pour our unparalleled collective efforts into the success of our retailers at this pivotal moment in our industry. As a New Zealand-based company, we’re proud to be globally recognized for the product and company we have built and are excited about this next step in our journey.” </span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/lightspeed-to-acquire-vend-to-power-global-retail-expansion-301245999.html">Click here to read the full release.</a> </span></i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/d649151a-blog_echo_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/d649151a-blog_echo_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Alix Fraser</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Revolutionizes Supply Chain of Independent Retailers with Launch of Supplier Network</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-supplier-network/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-supplier-network/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 17:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel commerce platforms, has announced the initial availability of the Lightspeed Supplier Network for North American retailers.  The launch of [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/0b4aef51-blog_news-section_20-launches-supplier-network_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/0b4aef51-blog_news-section_20-launches-supplier-network_1200x628.jpg" /><p><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=3033818-1&amp;h=1773015452&amp;u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel commerce platforms, has announced the initial availability of the </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=3033818-1&amp;h=4068384713&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2Flightspeed-supplier-market%2F%2520%E2%80%8E&amp;a=Lightspeed+Supplier+Network"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Supplier Network</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> for North American retailers. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The launch of the fully integrated stock ordering solution transforms supply chain management for SMBs, democratizing access to the strategic inventory visibility once reserved predominantly for enterprise retail and eCommerce giants as the global COVID-19 pandemic continues to place pressure on supply chains in 2021.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Revolutionizing the SMB-supplier relationship</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Supplier Network’s direct integration between businesses and brands provides merchants with an automatically updating supplier catalog system, easy order management tools and automated shipment handling directly within Lightspeed&#8217;s cloud-based platform.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It enables SMBs to more easily adopt a demand-focused inventory model to remain nimble, placing independent businesses on equal footing with large chains while providing suppliers access to a ready-to-buy customer base and real-time sell-through data.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;Connecting SMB retailers directly to their suppliers through the Lightspeed Supplier Network is nothing short of revolutionary. This new tool enables independent businesses to discover new products, more easily sell online and make better use of their capital to strategically increase order frequency,&#8221; said Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO of Lightspeed. &#8220;The disruption of 2020 cemented the need for SMBs to use technology to remain agile and the Supplier Network is deeply in line with Lightspeed&#8217;s mission to strengthen their operational resilience.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;With the growing demand for bicycle-related products and supply being lean, product curation and inventory visibility are key to success for SMBs,&#8221; said Charles Bisaillon, Retail Success Leader for Specialized Bicycle Components. &#8220;The direct integration our brand has with Lightspeed creates an ecosystem that ensures our retailers have full visibility of Specialized products to satisfy that growing demand, a critical capability in 2021.&#8221;</span></p>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key advantages of the Lightspeed Supplier Network</span></h3>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>A harmonized marketplace:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Provides the same direct supplier access and inventory visibility as the big box stores, easily managed through a single platform.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Automated manual ordering and consolidated supplier portals in the POS:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Improves transparency of when a shipment will arrive and what goods will be included, shortening the receiving cycle and getting items into consumers&#8217; hands more quickly.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>More discoverable new suppliers and products:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Product details, including photos, are imported into the POS with a click of a button, eliminating a barrier to selling online.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Increased control of supplier branding:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Easy import workflow for retailers ensures merchants are using brand-approved names, product descriptions and high-quality imagery.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Aggregated and anonymized sell-through data in real-time for suppliers:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Brands are granted unprecedented visibility of goods sold by independent merchants.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Lightspeed Supplier Network will be initially available for retailers in the bike, outdoor sport, jewelry and pet verticals. </span><a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/partners/supplier-network/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here for more information and to become part of the growing marketplace.</span></a></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2021/Lightspeed-Revolutionizes-Supply-Chain-of-Independent-Retailers-with-Launch-of-Supplier-Network/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here to learn more.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/0b4aef51-blog_news-section_20-launches-supplier-network_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/0b4aef51-blog_news-section_20-launches-supplier-network_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Alix Fraser</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Golf Operators in North America Outperform Industry in 2020</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-golf-outperform-industry/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-golf-outperform-industry/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 15:42:53 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel platforms, revealed customer growth insights for its clientele within the golf industry, highlighting operators in the United States and [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/4fb165f9-blog_news-section_01-golf-operators-outperform-2020_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/4fb165f9-blog_news-section_01-golf-operators-outperform-2020_1200x628.jpg" /><p><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=3014364-1&amp;h=2685900431&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fgolf%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel platforms, revealed customer growth insights for its clientele within the golf industry, highlighting</span><b> operators in the United States and Canada have grown 23% and 26% respectively </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">in course occupancy year-over-year for January to September 2020, a period marked by the digital revolution of golf operations similar to that witnessed in the retail and hospitality industries.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In contrast, according to the </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=3014364-1&amp;h=162986538&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.thengfq.com%2F2020%2F11%2Fafter-september-surge-rounds-8-7-year-to-date%2F&amp;a=National+Golf+Foundation"><span style="font-weight: 400;">National Golf Foundation</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NGF), industry average for rounds played increased by 8.7% (year-over-year, in the same time period). </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Indispensable digital strategies</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The data underscores the strategic role played by cloud-based technology in the operations of the golf industry&#8217;s highest-performing businesses in order to capitalize on significant new interest in the game, driven in part by COVID-19 measures.</span></p>
<p><b>&#8220;The ease and ability to seamlessly transition our business to a digital, contactless model while driving online reservations from 20% to 90% in a week reveals how indispensable Lightspeed has become as a tool for sustaining SMBs in 2020,&#8221;</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> said Del Ratcliffe, owner of five North Carolina-based golf course management businesses and a Lightspeed customer. </span><b>&#8220;It also showcases the strong prospects for golf&#8217;s continued growth in 2021 as course owners remain agile and competitive in the evolving industry.&#8221;</b></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed as the future of golf</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed now powers more than 1000 golf courses worldwide. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following a year of signing landmark deals with prestigious courses such as </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=3014364-1&amp;h=3520029601&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fnam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com%2F%3Furl%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fwww.newswire.ca%252Fnews-releases%252Flandscapes-golf-management-chooses-lightspeed-to-power-30-courses-in-the-u-s--852024294.html%26data%3D04%257C01%257CDashaun.Gasque%2540zenogroup.com%257Cf28e5e35f64d46646fb808d89bdb5bd4%257Cb824bfb3918e43c2bb1cdcc1ba40a82b%257C0%257C0%257C637430713728920205%257CUnknown%257CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%253D%257C1000%26sdata%3DiOG6w%252BeMaDsm4QLtFw2V%252FM4qYhlOHMVQ1tfPt%252B5aTxA%253D%26reserved%3D0&amp;a=Landscape+Golf+Management"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Landscape Golf Management</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, this new set of data indicates how </span><b>Lightspeed is positively impacting sales for independent businesses specifically within the golf and sports business sector</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">, helping business owners create safe, unique and adjustable customer experiences that drive brand loyalty with solutions.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Golf-Operators-in-North-America-Outperform-Industry-in-2020/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here to learn more.</span></i></a><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span></i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/4fb165f9-blog_news-section_01-golf-operators-outperform-2020_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/4fb165f9-blog_news-section_01-golf-operators-outperform-2020_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Alix Fraser</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Announces Acquisition of Upserve to Further Omnichannel Revolution of American Restaurant Industry</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-acquisition-of-upserve/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-acquisition-of-upserve/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 15:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed POS Inc. (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel commerce platforms, announced December 1, 2020, it has acquired Upserve Inc., a leading restaurant management cloud-software company [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/ac7d5fa6-blog_news-section_02-acquisition-upserve_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/ac7d5fa6-blog_news-section_02-acquisition-upserve_1200x628.jpg" /><p><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2998153-1&amp;h=2764444758&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F%3Frac%3Dtrue%26f%3DCA-EN&amp;a=Lightspeed+POS+Inc."><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed POS Inc.</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel commerce platforms, announced December 1, 2020, </span><b>it has acquired</b> <a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2998153-1&amp;h=1610949407&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fupserve.com%2F&amp;a=Upse"><b>Upse</b></a><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2998153-1&amp;h=3909670548&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fupserve.com%2F&amp;a=rve"><b>rve</b></a><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2998153-1&amp;h=917800100&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fupserve.com%2F&amp;a=%C2%A0Inc"><b> Inc</b></a><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2998153-1&amp;h=170329298&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fupserve.com%2F&amp;a=."><b>.</b></a><b>, a leading restaurant management cloud-software company</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> based in Rhode Island and a Vista Equity Partners portfolio company. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The acquisition strengthens Lightspeed&#8217;s position as an industry leader with high-performing restaurateurs across the United States as those restaurants refine the digital dining experience.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coming together to serve the future of hospitality</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The union of Lightspeed and Upserve will </span><b>accelerate product innovation and the advancement of Lightspeed&#8217;s analytics-driven commerce platform.</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> A convergence of the two companies&#8217; teams and technology will provide independent restaurants in the United States, from fine-dine to multi-location fast-casual, one of the most competitive hospitality platforms on the market and enable the industry to more easily navigate the new dining needs made permanent by the COVID-19 pandemic.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The acquisition builds on Lightspeed&#8217;s growth momentum following the company&#8217;s listing on the New York Stock Exchange and the acquisition of </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2998153-1&amp;h=2152735340&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.shopkeep.com%2F&amp;a=ShopKeep"><span style="font-weight: 400;">ShopKeep</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, a leading cloud commerce platform provider serving more than 20,000 customer locations. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Combining with Upserve will grow Lightspeed&#8217;s position in the U.S. hospitality market by an additional 7,000 customer locations generating over $6 billion in GTV in the trailing twelve-month period ending September 30, 2020.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Entering a new era of collaboration for Lightspeed and Upserve</span></h2>
<p><b>&#8220;Combining forces with Upserve is a strategic next-step in Lightspeed&#8217;s vision of providing the most advanced commerce platform to high-performing businesses around the world,&#8221; </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">said Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO of Lightspeed. &#8220;We believe this acquisition will accelerate the product innovation that has enabled Lightspeed customers to tackle the greatest challenge to their industry in decades and will add exceptional leadership to our teams in anticipation of the economic recovery of the global hospitality industry.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;Through its analytics-based POS and restaurant management solutions, Upserve has been delivering actionable insights to restaurateurs for over a decade. Lightspeed is quickly emerging as a world-leading commerce platform for SMBs and partnering with them to deliver data-based insights through a single digital hub was a natural choice&#8221;, said Upserve CEO Sheryl Hoskins. </span><b>&#8220;Together we look forward to empowering North American restaurateurs to deliver superior guest experiences and make them wildly successful.&#8221;</b></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Details of transaction</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Upserve generated revenue of approximately $40 million for the trailing twelve-month period ending September 30, 2020. Lightspeed acquired Upserve for estimated total consideration of  $430 million, consisting of approximately $123 million in net cash and up to 5,895,365 subordinate voting shares in the capital of Lightspeed, subject to customary post-closing adjustments.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Management hosted a conference call to discuss the transaction at 5:30 PM EST on December 1, 2020. The webcast was available live on the </span><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Investors section of the Company&#8217;s website</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">RBC Capital Markets acted as financial advisor to Lightspeed on the transaction and William Blair acted as advisor to Upserve.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Announces-Acquisition-of-Upserve-to-Further-Omnichannel-Revolution-of-American-Restaurant-Industry/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here to learn more.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/ac7d5fa6-blog_news-section_02-acquisition-upserve_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/ac7d5fa6-blog_news-section_02-acquisition-upserve_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Alix Fraser</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Appoints Manon Brouillette to its Board of Directors</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-appoints-manon-brouillette/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-appoints-manon-brouillette/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 16:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed POS Inc. (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a global commerce leader, recently announced the appointment of distinguished technology CEO Manon Brouillette to its board of directors.  Brouillette brings valuable insights [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/80eeabf5-blog_news-section_03-manon-brouillette_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/80eeabf5-blog_news-section_03-manon-brouillette_1200x628.jpg" /><p><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2991227-1&amp;h=3949800448&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+POS+Inc."><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed POS Inc.</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a global commerce leader, recently announced the appointment of distinguished technology CEO </span><b>Manon Brouillette </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">to its board of directors. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brouillette brings valuable insights and a fresh perspective as Lightspeed actively rolls out new innovations in cloud-based technology for SMBs in the retail, hospitality, and golf industries. As one of Canada&#8217;s 100 Most Powerful Women, she will provide superior expertise as a former executive who led telecommunications giant, Videotron.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">The next step in innovation for Brouillette</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In her previous role as CEO of Videotron, Brouillette spearheaded a series of large-scale strategic rollouts until January 2019. This included Videotron&#8217;s entry into the wireless market ($1B investment), making the company Canada&#8217;s fastest-growing carrier, and transforming the cable television business model into a multiplatform, on-demand and linear video service. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since then, she has worked as an advisor to venture capital and private equity firms, and sits on the board of Altice USA (NYSE:ATUS), National Bank of Canada (TSX:NA), Sonder and Ipsy.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;I&#8217;ve had the unique opportunity to closely watch Lightspeed scale its operations on a global level,&#8221; said Brouillette. &#8220;I&#8217;m thrilled to join Lightspeed&#8217;s board of directors during this pivotal moment in the company&#8217;s history. </span><b>I&#8217;ve long admired businesses that make up the fabric of their community, and I am eager to support Lightspeed&#8217;s mission to help complex SMBs accelerate business growth with the adoption of industry-leading digital solutions.&#8221;</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;We are truly grateful to have Manon Brouillette join our board of directors with her extensive experience establishing and growing technology leaders,&#8221; said Dax Dasilva, Lightspeed Founder and CEO. &#8220;Brouillette&#8217;s esteemed career transforming corporations for a new digital era adds another imperative voice of leadership that will drive our business forward.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Posed to serve the future of commerce</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Further demonstrating the company&#8217;s growth, Lightspeed recently announced its entry into a definitive purchase agreement to complete the landmark acquisition of </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2991227-1&amp;h=1468869615&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.shopkeep.com%2F&amp;a=ShopKeep"><span style="font-weight: 400;">ShopKeep</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, a leading cloud commerce platform provider based in New York City. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed has also released new innovations to support SMBs as they future-proof their businesses. This includes the recent launch of </span><b>Lightspeed Subscriptions</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">, a module that allows retailers to collect recurring revenue, and </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2991227-1&amp;h=3000012783&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fblog%2Flightspeed-capital%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Capital+powered+by+Stripe"><b>Lightspeed Capital powered by Stripe</b></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, a resource that provides select retailers with quick and easy financing. Within hospitality, this includes </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2991227-1&amp;h=326382998&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Frestaurant%2Fecom-restaurant%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+eCom+for+Restaurant"><b>Lightspeed eCom for Restaurant</b></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, a solution helping food service users seamlessly transition their businesses online, and </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2991227-1&amp;h=1076305571&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Frestaurant%2Forder-ahead%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Order+Ahead"><b>Lightspeed Order Ahead</b></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, a cost-efficient online ordering management system designed to facilitate takeout for restaurateurs seeking new revenue streams.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Appoints-Manon-Brouillette-to-its-Board-of-Directors/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here to learn more.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/80eeabf5-blog_news-section_03-manon-brouillette_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/80eeabf5-blog_news-section_03-manon-brouillette_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Alix Fraser</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Acquires ShopKeep to Accelerate Digital Transformation of SMBs Across the United States</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-acquires-shopkeep/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-acquires-shopkeep/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 16:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed POS Inc. (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel commerce platforms, recently announced it has entered into a definitive agreement to acquire ShopKeep Inc. (ShopKeep), a [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/079b788d-blog_news-section_04-acquisition-shopkeep_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/079b788d-blog_news-section_04-acquisition-shopkeep_1200x628.jpg" /><p><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2972137-1&amp;h=354666715&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+POS+"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed POS </span></a><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2972137-1&amp;h=4033379815&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Inc"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Inc</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading provider of cloud-based, omnichannel commerce platforms, recently announced </span><b>it has entered into a definitive agreement to acquire </b><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2972137-1&amp;h=3773839072&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.shopkeep.com%2F&amp;a=ShopKeep"><b>ShopKeep</b></a><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2972137-1&amp;h=700546130&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.shopkeep.com%2F&amp;a=%C2%A0Inc"><b> Inc</b></a><b>. </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">(ShopKeep), a leading cloud commerce platform provider based in New York City. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This acquisition reinforces Lightspeed&#8217;s status as a clear category leader for complex retailers and restaurateurs seeking to modernize their operations as the global economy undergoes unprecedented digital acceleration.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Joining forces to serve merchants</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">COVID-19 is forcing independent businesses to urgently replace legacy point-of-sale systems in order to remain operational and safely adapt to evolving consumer behaviors. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The scale achieved by the combination of Lightspeed and ShopKeep presents retail and restaurant business owners in the United States with enhanced resources to pivot their operations. Lightspeed&#8217;s analytics, loyalty, eCommerce and payments modules, in addition to its multi-location solution, will offer ShopKeep&#8217;s customer base the opportunity to enhance their capabilities.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The acquisition immediately expands Lightspeed&#8217;s U.S. market share, allowing for increased investment in sales, marketing and research and development to capitalize on the increasing demand for modern, cloud-based, omnichannel commerce solutions. Following the closing of the acquisition, </span><b>Lightspeed will serve over 100,000 customer locations worldwide, generating approximately $33 billion USD in gross transaction volume (GTV).</b></p>
<p><b>&#8220;ShopKeep&#8217;s commitment to enabling independent businesses to dream big and rise above industry and economic challenges is deeply aligned with our own mission to power the future of commerce,&#8221; </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">said Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO of Lightspeed. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;This acquisition will bring ShopKeep merchants, small and medium-sized businesses that make up the backbone of the U.S economy, into the Lightspeed family, providing them even more crucial product innovation and world-class support as they drive the reinvention of American commerce.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Uniting over a shared mission</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The acquisition will generate strong expected synergies resulting from increased GTV, the ability to leverage integrated go-to-market resources and a combined payments opportunity. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed&#8217;s acquisition of ShopKeep will follow the successful integration of multiple premier platforms that experienced accelerated growth following their acquisitions by Lightspeed, including that of Montréal-based Chronogolf, Sydney-based Kounta and Berlin-based Gastrofix.</span></p>
<p><b>&#8220;We believe uniting with Lightspeed highlights and amplifies our shared vision to deliver industry leading commerce enablement for small and medium-sized businesses,&#8221; </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">said Michael DeSimone, CEO of ShopKeep. &#8220;Our partnership sets the stage to help business owners navigate through challenging times, keep pace with rapid change and adapt quickly to meet the rising demands of today&#8217;s customers.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Details of transaction</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ShopKeep generated revenue of approximately $50 million and GTV of approximately $7 billion in the trailing twelve month period ending September 2020. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed will acquire ShopKeep for a total estimated consideration of approximately $440 million, satisfied by way of payment on closing of $145.2 million in cash and the issuance of 9,500,000 subordinate voting shares in the capital of Lightspeed. The deal, which is subject to customary closing conditions and post-closing working capital adjustment, closed before the end of the company&#8217;s quarter ending December 31, 2020. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additional details regarding this transaction were communicated during Lightspeed&#8217;s Fiscal Second Quarter 2021 Financial Results Conference Call, scheduled for Thursday, November 5, 2020.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">RBC Capital Markets acted as advisor to Lightspeed on the transaction.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-to-Acquire-ShopKeep-to-Accelerate-Digital-Transformation-of-SMBs-Across-the-United-States/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here to learn more.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/079b788d-blog_news-section_04-acquisition-shopkeep_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/079b788d-blog_news-section_04-acquisition-shopkeep_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Alix Fraser</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Unlocks New Revenue Stream for North American Retailers with the Launch of Subscriptions</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-subscriptions/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-subscriptions/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 15:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) recently announced the initial availability of Lightspeed Subscriptions, a new module that allows local retailers using Lightspeed Payments in North America to collect recurring revenue [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2884fc93-blog_news-section_05-launch-of-subscriptions_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/2884fc93-blog_news-section_05-launch-of-subscriptions_1200x628.jpg" /><p><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2955886-1&amp;h=942294682&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) recently announced the initial availability of Lightspeed Subscriptions, a new module that allows local retailers using </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2955886-1&amp;h=2717289771&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2Fpayments%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Payments"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Payments</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in North America to </span><b>collect recurring revenue seamlessly through their POS. </b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gaining a foothold within the thriving health and wellness vertical, Lightspeed introduces the new feature to provide retailers an innovative tactic to build customer loyalty and future-proof their business.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Equipping merchants to serve changing customer behavior</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nearly half of consumers will fundamentally change the way they shop as a result of COVID-19, with </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2955886-1&amp;h=1919436988&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ey.com%2Fen_us%2Fconsumer-products-retail%2Fhow-covid-19-could-change-consumer-behavior&amp;a=34+percent"><span style="font-weight: 400;">34 percent</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> indicating they would pay more for local products. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coupled with an increase in demand for subscription boxes and services driven by the global pandemic, </span><b>Lightspeed Subscriptions equips independent businesses with a vital sales strategy as consumers shop local and support their communities. </b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Subscriptions supports a multitude of complex SMBs at the core of Lightspeed&#8217;s retail customer base. For example, retailers can sell subscriptions that will regularly replenish a buyer&#8217;s favorite products or surprise customers with new specialty items every month. Other businesses like gyms or spas can offer subscriptions that grant consumers access to regular services or exclusive rewards.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;The introduction of Lightspeed Subscriptions further adds to our comprehensive toolbox of solutions for complex retailers,&#8221; said Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO of Lightspeed. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;Local retailers need to gear up for a dramatic shift in shopping habits. With this in mind, we&#8217;re equipping merchants with an exciting new service that promises a source of uninterrupted revenue and will continue to fuel their businesses into the New Year.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Securing revenue through Subscriptions</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key advantages of Lightspeed Subscriptions for local retailers include:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Provides Stable Revenue:</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">Recurring payments guarantees income at regular intervals, which merchants can depend on during unpredictable times</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Builds a Loyal Customer Base:</strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Convenient and personalized product/service offerings boost brand loyalty and customer retention</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Integrates Directly into POS:</strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> As an add-on to Lightspeed Retail, ensures simple and unified set-up within the existing POS platform</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Ensures Secure, Automated Payments:</strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Credit card information is securely stored for future automatic Subscription sales with customer consent (PCI Compliant). Failed payments are also automatically reprocessed and expired cards will continue to work, even as the bank replaces the physical card to ensure minimal interruption for the customer</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This latest solution follows several other recent Lightspeed innovations for retailers such as </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2955886-1&amp;h=2044916341&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fblog%2Flightspeed-mobile-tap%2F&amp;a=Mobile+Tap"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mobile Tap</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2955886-1&amp;h=102725833&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fblog%2Flightspeed-digital-wallet%2F&amp;a=Digital+Wallet"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Digital Wallet</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, and </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2955886-1&amp;h=751795327&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fblog%2Fanalytics-core%2F&amp;a=Analytics+Core"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Analytics Core</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Following this initial launch, Lightspeed also will be developing plans to roll out Lightspeed Subscriptions for eCommerce.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Unlocks-New-Revenue-Stream-for-North-American-Retailers-with-the-Launch-of-Subscriptions/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here for more information.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2884fc93-blog_news-section_05-launch-of-subscriptions_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2884fc93-blog_news-section_05-launch-of-subscriptions_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Alix Fraser</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Landscapes Golf Management Chooses Lightspeed to Power 30 Courses in the U.S.</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/landscapes-golf-management-lightspeed/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/landscapes-golf-management-lightspeed/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 14:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced that it has been selected by Landscapes Golf Management as the cloud-based commerce software that will power 30 of its prestigious golf courses [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/164867bb-blog_news-section_06-landscapes-golf-management_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/164867bb-blog_news-section_06-landscapes-golf-management_1200x628.jpg" /><p><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2942262-1&amp;h=2276192520&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed"><b>Lightspeed</b></a><b> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced that it has been selected by </b><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2942262-1&amp;h=74679247&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.landscapesunlimited.com%2Findex.php&amp;a=Landscapes+Golf%C2%A0Management"><b>Landscapes Golf Management</b></a><b> as the cloud-based commerce software that will power 30 of its prestigious golf courses in the U.S. </b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As one of the largest golf management organizations in the world with over 40 years in business, Landscapes Golf Management recognizes the benefits of managing all facets of its business in one simplified system, including its pro shops, clubhouses and golf courses. The golf leader adds Lightspeed&#8217;s solutions, including robust APIs, to an existing technology stack during a time of rapid digital transformation within the industry.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Adaptation in the face of challenges</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With government legislation permitting the continuation of golf operations in most of Landscapes Golf Management&#8217;s regions at the height of the pandemic, certain policies and precautions were introduced to ensure the safety of not only its golfers but its staff as well. With Lightspeed&#8217;s support, the company can now balance new policies with creative business concepts using cloud-based, mobile technology.</span></p>
<p><b>&#8220;Lightspeed has been a trusted partner for some time as we continue to digitally transform our business,&#8221; </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">says Scot Wellman, Landscapes Golf Management Director of Marketing and Revenue Management. </span></p>
<p><b>&#8220;With Lightspeed&#8217;s technology, we&#8217;ve been able to quickly build integrations that help us automate our systems, streamline processes, increase security and provide industry leading results that you can&#8217;t find anywhere else.</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> We hope to set an example through our innovations, and reinforce the notion that embracing technology is key to ensuring the golf industry&#8217;s long-term success.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed for digital transformation</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">How Lightspeed is helping Landscapes Golf Management digitally transform their businesses:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Offering Flexible Pre-Payment:</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">Supports a &#8220;no-touch&#8221; policy with an online function that enables golfers to pay remotely without having to enter a clubhouse</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Introducing Self Check-In Kiosk:</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">Allows golfers to practice social distancing and check-in virtually</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Granting Remote Working Capabilities:</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">Enables administrative tasks to be completed online using Lightspeed&#8217;s cloud-based platform</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Drawing Focus to the Customer:</strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Embraces a customer-centric approach by taking care of back-end operations. This allows the business to focus on a strong content strategy to inform its community and provide entertainment for its customers who are staying at home</span></li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Landscapes-Golf-Management-Chooses-Lightspeed-to-Power-30-Courses-in-the-U.S/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here for more information.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/164867bb-blog_news-section_06-landscapes-golf-management_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/164867bb-blog_news-section_06-landscapes-golf-management_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Alix Fraser</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Further Innovates Contactless Experience for Restaurants with the Launch of Order Ahead in North America</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-order-ahead/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-order-ahead/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 15:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced the availability of Order Ahead, a cost-efficient online ordering management system designed to facilitate takeout, enabling North American restaurants to provide customers with [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/bd5614ce-blog_news-section_07-launch-of-order-ahead_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/bd5614ce-blog_news-section_07-launch-of-order-ahead_1200x628.jpg" /><p><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2932837-1&amp;h=3472966502&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD)</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">has announced the availability of </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2932837-1&amp;h=418633650&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Frestaurant%2Forder-ahead%2F&amp;a=Order+Ahead"><b>Order Ahead</b></a><b>,</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> a cost-efficient online ordering management system designed to facilitate takeout, enabling North American restaurants to provide customers with a completely contactless dining experience. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meeting new hospitality challenges with technology</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As COVID-19 drives growth in the restaurant-to-consumer delivery market worldwide, hospitality businesses are turning to technology to reduce friction and high fees in the takeout and delivery experience. </span><b>Order Ahead integrates fully with Lightspeed eCom for Restaurant, creating a powerful digital hub that equips restaurants with new revenue streams as they future-proof their business.</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;As the pandemic continues to accelerate the digital transformation of the food service industry and consumers intend to make more takeout and delivery purchases, reaching diners outside restaurant walls has never been more important to ensuring long-term success,&#8221; said Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO of Lightspeed. &#8220;With Order Ahead,</span><b> restaurants can integrate a new sales channel directly into their existing POS and provide a contactless end-to-end experience.&#8221;</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key features and benefits of Order Ahead:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Seamless integration and real-time updates: </strong>Restaurants can accept orders made online that appear directly into the Lightspeed POS, streamlining all orders into the prep queue. Merchants can now send real-time status updates via text message, so customers can track their orders from start to end.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Convenient and contactless ordering:</strong> Offers customers a variety of safe and flexible pick-up and delivery choices, including the option to place an order for now or later and accept contactless payments.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Streamlined online experience: </strong>Provides users with the option to customize branding and adjust hours of operation, preparation time, as well as pick-up with curb-side options.</li>
</ul>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Offering a new suite of online hospitality tools</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;COVID-19 has changed how we run our business, and we knew we needed a technology partner that was fully integrated with an online ordering platform. Lightspeed and the Order Ahead integration is simple to use and keeps my staff safe,&#8221; says Juliana Carlucci, owner of </span><a href="https://happyburger.ca/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Happy Burger</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in Toronto, Ontario. </span><b>&#8220;We now know we can generate income in the coming months, even if the pandemic keeps dining rooms closed.&#8221;</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The launch of Order Ahead builds on Lightspeed&#8217;s innovative product suite for the hospitality industry.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Most recently, Lightspeed unveiled </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2932837-1&amp;h=6757865&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Frestaurant%2Fecom-restaurant%2F&amp;a=eCom+for+Restaurant"><span style="font-weight: 400;">eCom for Restaurant</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to help users seamlessly transition their businesses online. Whether for bespoke dishes, limited edition merchandise or grocery items, </span><b>this new eCom platform allows restaurants to continue to maintain strong customer relationships and diversify revenue.</b></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Further-Innovates-Contactless-Experience-for-Restaurants-with-the-Launch-of-Order-Ahead-in-North-America/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here for more information.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/bd5614ce-blog_news-section_07-launch-of-order-ahead_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/bd5614ce-blog_news-section_07-launch-of-order-ahead_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Alix Fraser</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Announces Initial Public Offering in the United States</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-usa-initial-public-offering/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-usa-initial-public-offering/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 15:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed POS Inc. (&#8220;Lightspeed&#8221; or the &#8220;Company&#8221;) (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) recently announced the launch of a marketed public offering of Lightspeed&#8217;s subordinate voting shares in the United States and [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/43b0b36a-blog_news-section_08-us-ipo_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/43b0b36a-blog_news-section_08-us-ipo_1200x628.jpg" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed POS Inc. (&#8220;Lightspeed&#8221; or the &#8220;Company&#8221;) (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) recently announced the launch of a marketed public offering of Lightspeed&#8217;s subordinate voting shares in the United States and Canada, representing </span><b>Lightspeed&#8217;s initial public offering in the United States.</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In connection with the initial public offering in the United States, Lightspeed filed an application to list its subordinate voting shares on the New York Stock Exchange (the &#8220;NYSE&#8221;) under the ticker &#8220;</span><b>LSPD</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;. Trading of Lightspeed&#8217;s subordinate voting shares commenced on the NYSE following pricing of the offering. Lightspeed&#8217;s subordinate voting shares will continue to trade on the Toronto Stock Exchange (the &#8220;TSX&#8221;) under the symbol &#8220;LSPD&#8221;.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Initial public offering share details</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A total of </span><b>11,650,000 subordinate voting shares </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">will be offered for sale under the offering, which will be conducted through a syndicate of underwriters led by Morgan Stanley, Barclays and BMO Capital Markets, as joint lead book-running managers, with BofA Securities and RBC Capital Markets as joint-bookrunners, and CIBC Capital Markets, KeyBanc Capital Markets, Raymond James, Scotiabank, TD Securities, and Truist Securities as co-managers. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">10,000,000 subordinate voting shares will be offered by Lightspeed from treasury and 1,650,000 subordinate voting shares will be offered by Caisse de dépôt et placement du Québec. The offering was priced in the context of the market with the price and total size of the offering to be determined at the time of entering into an underwriting agreement for the offering.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed and certain members of the Company&#8217;s management, including Dax Dasilva, will also grant the Underwriters an over-allotment option, exercisable for a period of 30 days from the date of the closing of the offering, to purchase up to </span><b>1,747,500 additional subordinate voting</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> shares, representing in the aggregate 15% of the total number of subordinate voting shares to be sold pursuant to the offering. Lightspeed will not receive any of the proceeds of the sale of subordinate voting shares by the selling shareholders.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Company currently expects that the net proceeds of the offering will be used primarily to strengthen the Company&#8217;s financial position and allow it to pursue its growth strategies. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key prospectus information</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Closing of the offering will be subject to a number of customary conditions, including the entering into of the definitive underwriting agreement, the listing of the subordinate voting shares issued by Lightspeed as part of the offering on the NYSE and the TSX, and any required approvals of the NYSE and the TSX.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In connection with the offering, Lightspeed filed, and obtained a receipt for, a second amended and restated short form base shelf prospectus, increasing the aggregate value of securities that may be distributed thereunder, and filed a preliminary prospectus supplement to such base shelf prospectus. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The base shelf prospectus and the preliminary prospectus supplement have been filed with the securities regulatory authorities in each of the provinces and territories of Canada, and have been filed with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission as part of a registration statement on Form F-10 under the U.S.-Canada multijurisdictional disclosure system (MJDS). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The public offering will be made in Canada only by means of the base shelf prospectus and preliminary prospectus supplement and in the United States only by means of the registration statement, including the base shelf prospectus and preliminary prospectus supplement. Such documents contain important information about the offering. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Copies of the base shelf prospectus and the preliminary prospectus supplement can be found on </span><a href="http://www.sedar.com"><span style="font-weight: 400;">SEDAR</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. A copy of the registration statement can be found on </span><a href="http://www.sec.gov"><span style="font-weight: 400;">EDGAR</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Copies of such documents may also be obtained from any of the following sources: </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Morgan Stanley, Attn: Prospectus Department &#8211; 180 Varick Street, 2nd Floor &#8211; New York, NY 10014</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Barclays, c/o Broadridge Financial Solutions, 1155 Long Island Avenue, Edgewood, NY 11717, telephone: (888) 603-5847, email: </span><a href="mailto:Barclaysprospectus@broadridge.com"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Barclaysprospectus@broadridge.com</span></a></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">BMO Capital Markets, Attn: Equity Syndicate Department, 3 Times Square, 25th Floor, New York, NY 10036, telephone: (800) 414-3627, email: </span><a href="mailto:bmoprospectus@bmo.com"><span style="font-weight: 400;">bmoprospectus@bmo.com</span></a></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brampton Distribution Centre c/o The Data Group of Companies, 9195 Torbram Road, Brampton, Ontario, L6S 6H2, telephone: (905) 791-3151 Ext. 4312, email: </span><a href="mailto:torbramwarehouse@datagroup.ca"><span style="font-weight: 400;">torbramwarehouse@datagroup.ca</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prospective investors should read the base shelf prospectus and the preliminary prospectus supplement as well as the registration statement before making an investment decision.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">No securities regulatory authority has either approved or disapproved the contents of this press release. This press release shall not constitute an offer to sell or the solicitation of an offer to buy nor shall there be any sale of the subordinate voting shares in any province, state or jurisdiction in which such offer, solicitation or sale would be unlawful prior to the registration or qualification under the securities laws of any such province, state or jurisdiction.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Announces-Initial-Public-Offering-in-the-United-States/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here for more information.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/43b0b36a-blog_news-section_08-us-ipo_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/43b0b36a-blog_news-section_08-us-ipo_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Alix Fraser</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Appoints Merline Saintil to its Board of Directors</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-appoints-merline-saintil/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-appoints-merline-saintil/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 14:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a global commerce leader, has announced the appointment of internationally recognized technology and engineering leader Merline Saintil to its board of directors.  As Lightspeed helps [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/beb51c3c-blog_news-section_09-merline-saintil_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/beb51c3c-blog_news-section_09-merline-saintil_1200x628.jpg" /><p><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2907157-1&amp;h=751432754&amp;u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a global commerce leader, has </span><b>announced the appointment of internationally recognized technology and engineering leader Merline Saintil to its board of directors. </b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As Lightspeed helps SMBs future-proof their businesses with innovative financial services and omnichannel solutions during a pivotal moment of growth, Saintil brings to the board years of experience developing award-winning products for Fortune 500 technology companies, including Intuit, Yahoo, and PayPal.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bringing proven expertise to the board</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Named one of the Women of Influence in 2017 by Silicon Valley Business Journal, one of the 22 Most Powerful Women Engineers in the World by Business Insider and earning a Lifetime Achievement Award from Girls in Tech, Saintil&#8217;s impressive career has not only made her a sought-after leader in the technology space, but has also broadened her expertise in cloud computing, mobile, online payments and commerce. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prior to her role as head of operations for the office of the CTO at Intuit, Saintil was instrumental in the platform shift to mobile at Yahoo where she was head of global engineering operations for mobile and emerging product.</span></p>
<p><b>&#8220;Lightspeed is leading the charge servicing diverse SMBs in the retail, hospitality, and golf industries with rapid innovation that meets the evolving needs of businesses located in over 100 countries,&#8221;</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> said Saintil. &#8220;I&#8217;m honored to join its board of directors and to have the opportunity to bring my experience in technology and engineering to supporting the company through future product development and growth.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taking on the future of commerce together</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;It is an absolute privilege to have Merline Saintil join our board of directors and bring her experience in Silicon Valley to support our ambitious goals here at Lightspeed,&#8221; said Dax Dasilva, Lightspeed founder and CEO. &#8220;Her skillset from working with other publicly-traded companies and her leadership will be invaluable as we look ahead to the future of Lightspeed.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To further equip merchants and hospitality businesses with the tools they need to succeed in the new normal and beyond, Lightspeed recently launched </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2907157-1&amp;h=1279633046&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fblog%2Flightspeed-capital%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Capital"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Capital</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to provide select retailers with quick and easy financing as well as </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2907157-1&amp;h=738291980&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Frestaurant%2Fecom-restaurant%2F&amp;a=eCommerce+for+Restaurant"><span style="font-weight: 400;">eCommerce for Restaurant</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2907157-1&amp;h=1941920917&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fblog%2Flightspeed-mobile-tap%2F&amp;a=Mobile+Tap"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mobile Tap</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Appoints-Merline-Saintil-to-its-Board-of-Directors/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here for more information.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/beb51c3c-blog_news-section_09-merline-saintil_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/beb51c3c-blog_news-section_09-merline-saintil_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Alix Fraser</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Launches eCom for Restaurants</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/ecom-for-restaurants/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/ecom-for-restaurants/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 14:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[As restaurants adapt to evolving global regulations when it comes to foodservice, Lightspeed (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced the release of eCom for Restaurant. The new Bon Appetit theme [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/03591c68-blog_news-section_10-launch-of-ecom-for-restaurants_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/03591c68-blog_news-section_10-launch-of-ecom-for-restaurants_1200x628.jpg" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As restaurants adapt to evolving global regulations when it comes to foodservice, </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2896122-1&amp;h=1923992127&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced the release of </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2896122-1&amp;h=1488888100&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Frestaurant%2Fecom-restaurant&amp;a=eCom+for+Restaurant"><span style="font-weight: 400;">eCom for Restaurant</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. The new Bon Appetit theme is </span><b>specifically designed to help </b><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2896122-1&amp;h=1743338969&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Frestaurant%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Restaurant"><b>Lightspeed Restaurant</b></a><b> users seamlessly transition their businesses online and integrate new revenue streams that will lead to long-term growth. </b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Channeling this need for reinvention, Lightspeed has partnered with McGill University and Canada Post to re-imagine the hospitality industry of the future. The white paper showcases insights that point to an omnichannel strategy being key for restaurant success as they navigate the new business landscape.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Digital transformation for hospitality businesses through eCommerce</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Businesses who use Lightspeed Restaurant and implement the Bon Appetit eCom template are better equipped to adapt to re-opening and the continuation of delivery and pick-up services.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Restaurateurs will benefit from an easy-to-set up and fully-customizable website that also includes several noteworthy features to help retain meaningful customer relationships and future-proof their business:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Display Menu and Unique Offerings for Sale</strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>:</strong> Publish digital menus that can be integrated with QR codes, showcase artisanal products, offer a curated selection of fresh produce and more</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Linking to Delivery Platforms:</strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Allows customers to conveniently order ahead online through integrations with key delivery partners such as Uber Eats and Order Ahead</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>OpenTable Integration:</strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Provides an easy-to-use reservation tool for customers by seamlessly connecting OpenTable to a restaurant&#8217;s website</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Instagram Integration:</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">Strengthens the online community by sharing inspiration, information and updates through an Instagram feed&#8217;s visibility on the website</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;The hospitality industry has been permanently altered by COVID-19 and as a leading technology company, it&#8217;s our responsibility to provide solutions that are designed to support the industry during this unprecedented time,&#8221; says Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO of Lightspeed.</span></p>
<p><b>&#8220;Our eCommerce for Restaurant solution equips restaurateurs with the right tools to establish their online presence and increase revenue, while also providing an online hub for their customers.&#8221;</b></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">McGill University, Lightspeed and Canada Post partner on the future of hospitality</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A new student-driven white paper published by McGill University in partnership with Lightspeed and Canada Post, titled </span><b>&#8220;The Hospitality Innovation Challenge,&#8221;</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> puts forth tactics restaurateurs should implement in order to future-proof their business, including adapting forward-looking technology and creating an omnichannel experience.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In &#8220;The Hospitality Innovation Challenge,&#8221; 80 teams of undergraduate and MBA students from 20 universities across Canada were invited to ideate actionable solutions to assist real businesses in finding a path to profitability as consumer behaviours continue to change. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Co-commissioned by enterprise and academia, the study sought to rethink the food sector for a post-pandemic world, revealing that the best ways for restauranteurs to pave a path to profitability were to expand their digital footprint, foster stronger customer relationships by rebuilding confidence, and stabilize cash flow through multiple revenue streams—most of which will be supported by the technology of Lightspeed&#8217;s eCom for Restaurant solution.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The full white paper can be viewed </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2896122-1&amp;h=2898450826&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fpdf.lightspeedhq.com%2Fwhite-papers%2FLightspeed-McGill-Hospitality-Innovation-Challenge-EN.pdf&amp;a=here"><span style="font-weight: 400;">here</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Launches-eCom-for-Restaurants/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here for more information</span></i></a><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/03591c68-blog_news-section_10-launch-of-ecom-for-restaurants_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/03591c68-blog_news-section_10-launch-of-ecom-for-restaurants_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Alix Fraser</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Capital Launches for U.S. Retail Customers</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-capital-launches-for-usa-retail/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-capital-launches-for-usa-retail/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 14:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Klara Roloff]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[As the retail industry continues to adopt innovative solutions amidst the global pandemic, Lightspeed (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced the initial availability of Lightspeed Capital, powered by Stripe.  Through [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2d07b95e-blog_news-section_11-lightspeed-capital_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/2d07b95e-blog_news-section_11-lightspeed-capital_1200x628.jpg" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As the retail industry continues to adopt innovative solutions amidst the global pandemic, </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2878058-1&amp;h=535097156&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed"><b>Lightspeed</b></a><b> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced the initial availability of </b><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2878058-1&amp;h=1641456040&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fblog%2Flightspeed-capital%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Capital"><b>Lightspeed Capital</b></a><b>, powered by </b><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2878058-1&amp;h=1612719589&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fstripe.com%2Fen-ca&amp;a=Stripe"><b>Stripe</b></a><b>.</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Through financing offers, this new product will help U.S.-based merchants with overall business growth, more specifically to buy inventory, invest in marketing or manage cash flows. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It is available for retailers using </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2878058-1&amp;h=2251826421&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2Fpayments%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Payments"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Payments</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in the U.S. and provides financing of up to $100,000 USD per retail location.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Funding to help retailers pursue their business goals</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Featured benefits of Lightspeed Capital for retailers include:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Fast and Efficient Approval Process: </strong><span style="font-weight: 400;">Unlike traditional financial institutions, there is no lengthy application or collateral obligations, and approved funds are typically deposited the next day</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Automated and Flexible Repayments:</strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> A percentage of daily sales will automatically be repaid against the borrowed amounts, keeping repayment flexible to suit the needs of the business</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Accessible Reporting:</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">Retailers can review how much has been repaid in real time with data built into Lightspeed&#8217;s software, providing one seamless platform to manage both payments and capital funds</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><strong>Data-Driven Eligibility:</strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Approval is based on a retailer&#8217;s history with Lightspeed Payments, and draws on data from Stripe&#8217;s global business network</span></li>
</ul>
<p><b>&#8220;Lightspeed retailers have always outperformed the broader industry</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">, and this has been more apparent than ever during COVID-19 as these innovative merchants have leveraged omnichannel solutions to meet customer demand,&#8221; said Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO of Lightspeed. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;The introduction of Lightspeed Capital is one more tool to help them digitally transform their business and continue to outpace the industry.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Supporting merchants for growth</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;We&#8217;re excited to help Lightspeed go the extra mile in building technology to make all aspects of running a modern retailer easier, from payments through to flexible financing,&#8221; Jeanne DeWitt Grosser, Head of Americas, Revenue and Growth at Stripe, commented. </span><b>&#8220;Extra capital can make all the difference for Lightspeed&#8217;s growing retailers who want to invest in adaptation as the economy reboots.&#8221;</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As part of Lightspeed&#8217;s continued effort to support merchants during this time, the company is hosting regular </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2878058-1&amp;h=2844494455&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fevents%2Fwebinars%2F&amp;a=webinars"><span style="font-weight: 400;">webinars</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to equip SMBs with essential information on financial planning, social media sales integrations, how to maximize retail revenue, and more.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Capital-Launches-for-U.S.-Retail-Customers/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here to learn more.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2d07b95e-blog_news-section_11-lightspeed-capital_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2d07b95e-blog_news-section_11-lightspeed-capital_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Klara Roloff</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Launches New Features to Drive Digital Transformation of Retail SMBs</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-launches-new-features/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-launches-new-features/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 14:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Klara Roloff]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[As SMBs navigate a new retail landscape permanently altered by COVID-19, technology adoption is pivotal to business success. In light of this, Lightspeed (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced new [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/b836f0a2-blog_news-section_12-new-feature-launches-retail_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/b836f0a2-blog_news-section_12-new-feature-launches-retail_1200x628.jpg" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As SMBs navigate a new retail landscape permanently altered by COVID-19, technology adoption is pivotal to business success. In light of this, </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2871532-1&amp;h=2868912203&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=%C2%A0Lightspeed"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced new features to help its customers with the continued digital transformation of their businesses. </span></p>
<p><b>The new tools offer increased mobility when processing transactions, more options for viewing business insights and will better support SMBs as they continue to adjust to consumer behaviour.</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Lightspeed has introduced business-empowering features for in-store POS and eCommerce, including </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2871532-1&amp;h=1247420902&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Flightspeed-mobile-tap%2F&amp;a=Mobile+Tap"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mobile Tap</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> supporting curbside pick-up and contactless payment, Digital Wallet and Analytics Core.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Developing technology to adapt to the future of commerce</span></h2>
<p><b>&#8220;Our priority as we look to the future of retail is to enable our customers to adapt quickly to the dramatic and rapid changes in consumer behaviour over the past few months,&#8221; </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">said Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO of Lightspeed. &#8220;The SMBs that Lightspeed powers are innovating quickly because they are equipped with tools that help them remain agile, stay connected with their customers, and future-proof their businesses.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The digital overhaul forced by COVID-19 has become the new normal, with consumer trends showing that eCommerce will remain crucial as SMBs adopt tactics to elevate the digital experience for their customers. Lightspeed&#8217;s new solutions enhance the omnichannel shopping experience, enable greater multi-location efficiencies, and offer opportunities for improved productivity for Lightspeed retailers.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mobile Tap for curbside pick-up and contactless payment</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed merchants in the U.S. using Lightspeed Payments will now be able to </span><b>process transactions with just a tap, anywhere in-store or curbside, offering greater flexibility in situations of social distancing. </b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Mobile Tap hardware connects through Bluetooth, essentially turning an iPad into a contactless mobile payments terminal. Payments are processed securely with the integration of end-to-end encryption technology.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Digital Wallet for eCommerce</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Optimized for mobile, the introduction of Digital Wallet in North America supports</span><b> faster eCommerce conversion and supports a plethora of payment methods globally,</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> including Google Pay<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> and Apple Pay®. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With 21% of U.S. eCommerce shoppers abandoning their cart at checkout due to a lengthy or complicated process, this secure and seamless one-click eCommerce checkout experience is part of the answer to improved conversion online.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Analytics Core for retail insights</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Through this new module, users will have access to a variety of business dashboards and insights on sales, inventory and employee performance, </span><b>enabling retailers to make data-driven decisions about the future.</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Analytics Core will be released globally and is the perfect entry point to Lightspeed&#8217;s existing retail analytics suite.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While it was integral for retailers to have an online presence during pandemic shutdowns, it has become clear that their digital presence and strategies will remain crucial. Retailers who utilize these tactics, combined with a deep understanding of their customers will come out ahead.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Launches-New-Features-to-Drive-Digital-Transformation-of-Retail-SMBs/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here to learn more.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/b836f0a2-blog_news-section_12-new-feature-launches-retail_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/b836f0a2-blog_news-section_12-new-feature-launches-retail_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Klara Roloff</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Unveils New eCommerce Features as SMBs Transform Their Businesses Digitally</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-new-ecommerce-features/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-new-ecommerce-features/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 14:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Klara Roloff]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[As commerce shifts toward fast and efficient online shopping and personalized experiences for limited and distanced in-store visits, Lightspeed POS Inc. (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced the release of [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/585c5fe7-blog_news-section_13-new-ecommerce-features_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/585c5fe7-blog_news-section_13-new-ecommerce-features_1200x628.jpg" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As commerce shifts toward fast and efficient online shopping and personalized experiences for limited and distanced in-store visits, </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2831737-1&amp;h=2759868411&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+POS+Inc."><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed POS Inc.</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced the release of new </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2831737-1&amp;h=2829998821&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fecommerce%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+eCommerce"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed eCommerce</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> features that will strengthen its omnichannel experience. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">eCommerce more important than ever</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2016, Lightspeed became an early innovator, introducing SMBs to a powerful eCommerce solution that synced with its existing in-store platform. </span></p>
<p><b>The company saw a 400% increase in eCommerce volumes processed by its retailers in April 2020, as compared to February</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">, illustrating that merchants who adopted Lightspeed eCommerce to power their online business were able to adapt quickly to changing consumer behavior in the wake of the COVID-19 pandemic.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As the global economy begins to re-open and entrepreneurs enter a new paradigm of business, Lightspeed has advanced its eCommerce onboarding process with 24/7 customer service available to new and existing merchants, supporting an increased volume of customers in going online and integrating the latest features into their operations. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Equipping merchants with even more robust eCommerce tools</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Recent new features include Live Preview Themes, which allows merchants to test the look of their online store prior to going live, and Multi-Location Inventory. This gives SMBs the ability to display to consumers their inventory availability for all store locations online so no sale is missed.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Customers can also take advantage of a plethora of integrations available on the app store, working seamlessly with its multi-channel and multi-currency system, opening up a new world of selling possibilities.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed merchants will also benefit from digital tools such as:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Lightspeed Shipping:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> An enhanced shipping broker service so Lightspeed merchants have immediate access to shipping rates and labels via Lightspeed eCommerce</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Curbside Pick-Up:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Enables consumers to shop curbside for convenience and flexibility</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Personalized Shopping:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Allows consumers to make appointments at their favorite merchants in a risk-free environment, building loyal relationships with store experts</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;Lightspeed is a company that helps retailers and restaurants become digital, and by introducing these eCommerce features, we&#8217;re able to address the immediate business needs of SMBs,&#8221; says Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO of Lightspeed. </span></p>
<p><b>&#8220;Omnichannel is no longer a nice-to-have, it&#8217;s a must-have,</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and it is important for us to constantly innovate in the retail, eCommerce and hospitality space, so we can continue to support retailers and restaurants as they digitally transform their business.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">eCommerce powered growth</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;We know from our customers that they find our website easy to navigate and that check out is seamless–both on a desktop and, more importantly these days, on their mobile devices,&#8221; says Lightspeed customer Simon Tooley, Founder &amp; President of </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2831737-1&amp;h=524582297&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.etiket.ca%2Fus%2F&amp;a=Etiket."><span style="font-weight: 400;">Etiket.</span></a> <b>&#8220;When we moved to Lightspeed eCommerce in 2017, we saw a jump in sales. </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">We are seeing double-digit growth year-over-year, and part of that is because our focus is on our customers, new products and growth opportunities, rather than having to manage the platform.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To further equip merchants, Lightspeed officially launched </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2831737-1&amp;h=810939408&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fblog%2Fpresenting-omnichannel-loyalty%2F&amp;a=Omni+Loyalty"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Omni Loyalty</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> last month, which allows retailers to build out their loyalty program with integrated offers and experiences seamlessly shared through both their online shop and their brick-and-mortar store.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Unveils-New-eCommerce-Features-as-SMBs-Transform-Their-Businesses-Digitally/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here for more information.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/585c5fe7-blog_news-section_13-new-ecommerce-features_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/585c5fe7-blog_news-section_13-new-ecommerce-features_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Klara Roloff</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Ivanhoé Cambridge teams up with Lightspeed to provide omnichannel solutions to small and medium-sized tenants in its Canadian shopping centres</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/ivanhoe-cambridge-lightspeed/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/ivanhoe-cambridge-lightspeed/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 14:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Klara Roloff]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Leading cloud-based point-of-sale solution provider Lightspeed POS Inc. (&#8220;Lightspeed&#8221; or the &#8220;Company&#8221;) (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) announced in 2020 a partnership with real estate industry leader Ivanhoé Cambridge (IC) to [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/9d7c8db6-blog_news-section_14-ivanhoe-cambridge_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/9d7c8db6-blog_news-section_14-ivanhoe-cambridge_1200x628.jpg" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Leading cloud-based point-of-sale solution provider </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2821284-1&amp;h=3894711567&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+POS+Inc."><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed POS Inc.</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (&#8220;Lightspeed&#8221; or the &#8220;Company&#8221;) (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) announced in 2020 a partnership with real estate industry leader Ivanhoé Cambridge (IC) to bring free and fully-integrated cloud services, including </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2821284-1&amp;h=1404066603&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Retail"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Retail</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2821284-1&amp;h=1670938379&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Frestaurant%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Restaurant"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Restaurant</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, to small and medium-sized tenants and restaurateurs with locations in Ivanhoé Cambridge Canadian shopping centers. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Giving merchants the tools to thrive</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;During these unprecedented times, it&#8217;s important to support our tenants. We understand that </span><b>consumer expectations and shopping habits are evolving,&#8221;</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> said Natahlie Palladitcheff, President and Chief Executive Officer at Ivanhoé Cambridge. &#8220;This is an opportunity, and we are proud to partner with Lightspeed to offer a safe, fluid and trusted omnichannel sales solution to our tenants wishing to serve the communities in which our shopping centres are located.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As economies gradually resume across the country, the partnership between the two Canadian-based companies will support businesses by offering Ivanhoé Cambridge small and medium tenants and restaurateurs, with a local or regional footprint with nascent eCommerce operations, one-year free access to an integrated, omnichannel sales solution. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tenants will also have access to modules such as </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2821284-1&amp;h=3825922065&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fecommerce%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+eCommerce"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed eCommerce</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2821284-1&amp;h=4180282062&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Frestaurant%2Fdelivery%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Delivery"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Delivery</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> built within the retail and restaurant platforms, respectively.</span></p>
<p><b>&#8220;Our goal is to ensure the small and medium-sized businesses in our cities—who are integral to the local economies—have access to the tools they need to be successful through these significant changes in consumer behaviour</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and as regulations for a staggered re-opening of retail centres and store fronts begin,&#8221; said JP Chauvet, President, Lightspeed POS Inc. &#8220;An omnichannel sales platform will support their needs in the short-term, while also fuelling the big picture as we look ahead to a post-COVID environment.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Benefits for merchants looking to adapt to the future with Lightspeed</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">What the partnership Means for retailers who adopt Lightspeed Retail:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">An omnichannel point of sale (POS) solution that includes Lightspeed eCommerce and </span><b>opens inventory to an increasingly digitally savvy consumer base</b></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Must-have tools to engage customers</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">, including comprehensive loyalty programs, synchronized inventory management, and built-in reports with real-time sales data</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Integration of local and national parcel delivery</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">, via eCommerce</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">What the partnership means for restaurants who adopt Lightspeed Restaurant:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Lightspeed Delivery integration</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> options to Uber Eats, and other local food delivery services</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Reach more customers</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> by maximizing delivery zones, customizing a takeout menu, connecting to social media and using data to understand ordering patterns</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Options such as </span><b>self-order kiosks or tableside service with an iPad POS system</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> for in-restaurant experiences when doors reopen</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The launch of the partnership follows the announcement of new initiatives from Lightspeed to help SMBs sustain and protect their business during COVID-19, including, namely, select free services for three months, an </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2821284-1&amp;h=4212801571&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fcovid-19%2F&amp;a=online+resource+guide"><span style="font-weight: 400;">online resource guide</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, free </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2821284-1&amp;h=4121657308&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fevents%2Fwebinars%2F&amp;a=online+webinars"><span style="font-weight: 400;">online webinars</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with industry experts and the </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2821284-1&amp;h=3189699245&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fblog%2Flightspeed-local%2F&amp;a=%23LightspeedLocal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">#LightspeedLocal</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> campaign that reimbursed employees up to $500 in local currency on purchases made from any Lightspeed retail or restaurant customer.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Ivanho-Cambridge-teams-up-with-Lightspeed-to-provide-omnichannel-solutions-to-small-and-medium-sized-tenants-in-its-Canadian-shopping-centres/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here for more information.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/9d7c8db6-blog_news-section_14-ivanhoe-cambridge_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/9d7c8db6-blog_news-section_14-ivanhoe-cambridge_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Klara Roloff</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Collaborates with the CQCD to Make Cloud Commerce More Accessible to Retailers</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-collaborates-cqcd/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-collaborates-cqcd/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 14:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Klara Roloff]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed POS Inc. (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced a collaboration with the Conseil Québécois du Commerce de Détail (CQCD) to provide Québec-based retailers with personalized assistance and point-of-sale solutions, [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/db84dc8c-blog_news-section_15-cqcd_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/db84dc8c-blog_news-section_15-cqcd_1200x628.jpg" /><p><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2808867-1&amp;h=2759330023&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+POS+Inc."><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed POS Inc.</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced a collaboration with the Conseil Québécois du Commerce de Détail (CQCD) to provide Québec-based retailers with personalized assistance and point-of-sale solutions, to </span><b>help businesses adapt to changes in consumer behaviour during this disruptive time. </b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Retailers in the City of Montréal, Saint-Jérôme, and other Québec communities will be offered discounted access to Lightspeed&#8217;s </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2808867-1&amp;h=2939761378&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2Fomnichannel%2F&amp;a=omnichannel"><span style="font-weight: 400;">omnichannel</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> solutions. </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2808867-1&amp;h=535611075&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Retail"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Retail</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, which works seamlessly with </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2808867-1&amp;h=2824236537&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fecommerce%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+eCommerce"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed eCommerce</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, will provide new business channels to SMBs as the economy begins to re-open.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Developing technology for SMB merchants</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since Lightspeed launched its innovative omnichannel product in 2016, the company has continued to perfect and update the offering to suit the needs of the modern-day retailer. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the past four years, the company has introduced impactful product modules, including </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2808867-1&amp;h=3820729561&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2Fanalytics%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Analytics"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Analytics</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2808867-1&amp;h=3388343927&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2Floyalty%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Loyalty"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Loyalty</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2808867-1&amp;h=3267285976&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2Faccounting%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Accounting"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Accounting</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2808867-1&amp;h=2740772532&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2Fpayments%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Payments"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Payments</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><b>Benefits of Lightspeed&#8217;s omnichannel solution for retailers:</b></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Seamless integration of eCommerce with brick-and-mortar stores</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Easy-to-accept payments, synchronized inventory, and access to sales data, in-store and online</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Connections with customers on multiple platforms, enabling customers to shop at 24/7</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Product pickup and shipping flexibility</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">24/7 support available to all retailers</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;We understand that when retailers have the capability to meet their customers where they are, 24 hours a day and seven days a week, that it puts these businesses at a huge advantage—especially in the current climate,&#8221; says JP Chauvet, President, Lightspeed POS Inc. </span><b>&#8220;Our collaboration with the CQCD provides retailers with meaningful advice and access to digital resources that are integral to how they continue doing business during this time.&#8221;</b></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Giving back to Lightspeed’s home town</span></h2>
<p><b>&#8220;We&#8217;re thrilled to have a local Montréal-based technology company on board with our mission to support retailers in Québec and address the unique circumstances they are facing at this time,&#8221; </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">says Stéphane Drouin, General Director, CQCD. &#8220;As we assess the immediate needs retail businesses and whether there is value for them to activate an online presence, Lightspeed products are one of the viable solutions we&#8217;re able to offer.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Headquartered in Montréal, Lightspeed prides itself on the success on the independent merchants who make up the fabric of the community. The company will continue to provide access to essential technology and tools for the city of Montréal, Saint-Jérôme and others, through its collaboration with the CQCD.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Other recent initiatives from Lightspeed to help SMBs protect their business during COVID-19, include select free services for three months, free </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2808867-1&amp;h=3120030260&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fevents%2Fwebinars%2F&amp;a=online+webinars"><span style="font-weight: 400;">online webinars</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with industry experts and the </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2808867-1&amp;h=4064440133&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fblog%2Flightspeed-local%2F&amp;a=%23LightspeedLocal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">#LightspeedLocal</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> campaign that reimbursed employees up to $500 in local currency on purchases made from any Lightspeed retail or restaurant customer.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Collaborates-with-the-CQCD-to-Make-Cloud-Commerce-More-Accessible-to-Retailers/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here for more information.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/db84dc8c-blog_news-section_15-cqcd_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/db84dc8c-blog_news-section_15-cqcd_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Klara Roloff</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Introduces Initiatives Supporting Local Businesses</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-supporting-local-businesses/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-supporting-local-businesses/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 14:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Klara Roloff]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed POS Inc. (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) announced several initiatives in 2020 to support its local retail and restaurant customers who have been affected by the global COVID-19 pandemic. From [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/74c35611-blog_news-section_16-initiatives-supporting-local-business_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/74c35611-blog_news-section_16-initiatives-supporting-local-business_1200x628.jpg" /><p><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2757989-1&amp;h=693126205&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+POS+Inc."><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed POS Inc.</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) announced several initiatives in 2020 to support its local retail and restaurant customers who have been affected by the global COVID-19 pandemic. From March to June 2020, Lightspeed offered the following services for free to help customers adapt:</span><b></b></p>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1"><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2757989-1&amp;h=945740796&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Frestaurant%2Fdelivery%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Delivery"><b>Lightspeed Delivery</b></a><b> for restaurant customers</b></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1"><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2757989-1&amp;h=629023011&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fecommerce%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+eCommerce"><b>Lightspeed eCommerce</b></a><b> for retail customers</b></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1"><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2757989-1&amp;h=1155418797&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2Floyalty%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Loyalty"><b>Lightspeed Loyalty</b></a><b> for omnichannel customers</b></li>
</ul>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Local</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition, and to directly support our businesses, Lightspeed has also rolled out a #lightspeedlocal initiative that engages its company employees to shop locally and support small businesses in our network. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The program reimbursed employees in its 14 global offices up to $500 in local currency on purchases employees make from any Lightspeed retail or restaurant customer, whether through eCommerce shopping, meal takeout or delivery.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;Our employees and customers are at the heart of everything we do, and during this time of social distancing and uncertainty, it is more important than ever that we support them in a tangible way,&#8221; said Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO of Lightspeed. </span><b>&#8220;I&#8217;m inspired by the spirit and innovation from some of our customers leveraging omni and creative home delivery options to make the best of an incredibly difficult time. Helping others do the same is at the heart of these incentives that we are putting in place.&#8221;</b></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Looking out for our merchants</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our efforts aim to help small and medium-sized businesses remain agile in the current socio-economic climate and provide them with resources to safeguard a prosperous future.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On the heels of its recent bought deal offering, which closed February 27, 2020, Lightspeed remains well capitalized to support its highly diversified retail and restaurant customer base through this difficult time. </span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Introduces-Initiatives-Supporting-Local-Businesses/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here for more information.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/74c35611-blog_news-section_16-initiatives-supporting-local-business_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/74c35611-blog_news-section_16-initiatives-supporting-local-business_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Klara Roloff</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Launches New Integrated Payment Capabilities in North America</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/new-integrated-payments-north-america/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/new-integrated-payments-north-america/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 15:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Klara Roloff]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed POS (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced the initial availability of Lightspeed Payments for hospitality merchants in the United States and retailers in Canada.  Eliminating the need for a [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/01d50705-blog_news-section_17-launch-of-integrated-payments_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/01d50705-blog_news-section_17-launch-of-integrated-payments_1200x628.jpg" /><p><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2712844-1&amp;h=3879003150&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+POS"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed POS</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) has announced the initial availability of </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2712844-1&amp;h=866336867&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2Fpayments%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+Payments"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Payments</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> for hospitality merchants in the United States and retailers in Canada. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Eliminating the need for a separate payments provider, new and existing Lightspeed customers will benefit from Lightspeed Payments&#8217; direct integration with the commerce platform that saw its merchants growing </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2712844-1&amp;h=3188896468&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fblog%2Fyear-in-review%2F&amp;a=faster"><span style="font-weight: 400;">faster</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> than industry averages in 2019.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bringing integrated payments technology to even more businesses</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With Payments technology at their fingertips, even more SMBs now have access to true end-to-end customer service and sophisticated technology to improve their clients&#8217; checkout experience. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Operating from one system of record, merchants across North America can leverage the suite of modules that make up the Lightspeed platform to operate strategically from a single backend.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;Merchants are taking advantage of cloud technology to increasingly streamline operations and generate a tangible return on investment,&#8221; says Dax Dasilva, founder and CEO of Lightspeed. </span><b>&#8220;Lightspeed Payments provides customers the simplicity they desire to optimize their time and grow their business.&#8221;</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key features of Lightspeed Payments include:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Transparent Pricing and Cost Certainty:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> No startup fees and credit card-agnostic standard rates for card-present transactions, card-not-present transactions and keyed-in transactions. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Simplified Set-Up: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Frictionless process to get businesses transactional quickly and painlessly. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Fast and Secure Checkout Experience:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Supports all major payment methods and processes refunds without having to ask the cardholder to present their card. PCI compliant solution that helps SMBs combat fraud risk with monitoring and payments experts readily available to help when needed. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>One Place to Manage the Business: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">With one source of data and one company to trust, SMBs can manage their businesses in one place, including financial reporting and cash flow tracking.</span></li>
</ul>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed partners with Stripe to expand processing options for merchants</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now partnered with global payments processing platform </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2712844-1&amp;h=3585818995&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fstripe.com%2Fen-ca&amp;a=Stripe"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Stripe</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, Lightspeed Payments offers merchants a variety of processing options to best suit their business. This partnership enables Lightspeed Payments to now offer a faster checkout experience, improved reporting, and sleek new hardware well-suited for ambitious omnichannel merchants.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;Lightspeed Payments is extraordinarily easy to use and has modernized the way we run our business,&#8221; says </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2712844-1&amp;h=777713272&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.shopatlabel.com%2F&amp;a=LABEL+Boutique"><span style="font-weight: 400;">LABEL Boutique</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> owner Sarah Barton. </span><b>&#8220;Implementing a payments solution that was directly integrated with my point-of-sale system has eased the burden on my staff and led to a smoother customer experience. </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&#8217;s a nice touch that Stripe&#8217;s modern terminals blend in with the carefully curated aesthetic of my brick-and-mortar shop.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;Lightspeed has been simplifying business for retailers and restaurants for 15 years, and we&#8217;re excited to partner with them,&#8221; said John Collison, President and Co-founder of Stripe. &#8220;The fit and finish of Lightspeed&#8217;s new payment capabilities will delight their customers.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Today&#8217;s announcement furthers Lightspeed&#8217;s commitment to the more than 74,000 customer locations it supports throughout the globe and extends the Lightspeed Payments beyond retail and outside of the United States, where the company has offered the solution since January 2019.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Launches-New-Integrated-Payment-Capabilities-in-North-America/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here for more information.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/01d50705-blog_news-section_17-launch-of-integrated-payments_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/01d50705-blog_news-section_17-launch-of-integrated-payments_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Klara Roloff</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed Retailers Grew Over Six Times Faster Than Industry Average in Canada</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-retailers-grew-over-six-times-faster-than-industry-canada/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-retailers-grew-over-six-times-faster-than-industry-canada/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 15:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Klara Roloff]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed POS (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) revealed customer growth insights from its 2019 Year in Review, highlighting that retailers in Canada powered by Lightspeed saw 10.3% growth in year-over-year gross [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/0be1ae2f-blog_news-section_18-retailers-grew-six-times-faster_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/0be1ae2f-blog_news-section_18-retailers-grew-six-times-faster_1200x628.jpg" /><p><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2712844-1&amp;h=3879003150&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+POS"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed POS</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD) revealed customer growth insights from its </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2703921-2&amp;h=2144090643&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fpdf.lightspeedhq.com%2Fwhite-papers%2F2019-Retail-Year-In-Review-CAN.pdf&amp;a=2019+Year+in+Review"><span style="font-weight: 400;">2019 Year in Review</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, highlighting that </span><b>retailers in Canada powered by Lightspeed saw 10.3% growth in year-over-year gross transaction volume</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (GTV) for January to October 2019 compared to the same time period in 2018. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In contrast, industry average retail GTV during this time grew slightly (up 1.5% year-over-year), according to Statistics Canada, supporting the direct impact of cloud-based POS on retail sales amidst shifting global trends.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When data was measured against Lightspeed&#8217;s North American retail customers, </span><b>the results also showed significant year-over-year GTV growth for retailers powered by Lightspeed in the U.S.</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (13.8% in the same period), suggesting the competitive edge offered by Lightspeed extends to retailers across the border, a market with a similar fundamentals, although much greater in size.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additional Year in Review highlights</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed&#8217;s 2019 Retail Year in Review reveals how small and medium-sized retailers sustained growth, with noteworthy success in the sporting goods and health and beauty verticals: </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Sporting goods:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> The average number of transactions per merchant increased by over 22% for Lightspeed sporting goods retailers in 2019, reflecting how service offerings are attracting new customers while retaining loyal ones.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Health and beauty:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> With a massive rise in beauty influencers, overall sales for Lightspeed health and beauty retailers in 2019 increased by 24%.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;The 2019 Retail Year in Review demonstrates how Lightspeed is helping retailers outperform their peers across a range of industries using our innovative cloud-based technology,&#8221; says Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO of Lightspeed. </span></p>
<p><b>&#8220;It also reveals the degree to which Lightspeed has become an indispensable tool for SMBs in 2019 and showcases the strong prospects for retailers&#8217; continued growth in 2020 as they remain agile and competitive in the evolving retail industry.&#8221;</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This new data is an indicator of how Lightspeed is impacting sales for SMB retailers, helping businesses create unique customer experiences that drive brand loyalty with solutions such as</span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2703921-2&amp;h=943120741&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2Floyalty%2F&amp;a=%C2%A0Lightspeed+Loyalty"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Lightspeed Loyalty</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2703921-2&amp;h=980627201&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2Fanalytics%2F&amp;a=%C2%A0Lightspeed+Analytics"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Analytics</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2703921-2&amp;h=2383634131&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2Fpayments%2F&amp;a=%C2%A0Lightspeed+Payments"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed Payments</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-Retailers-Grew-Over-Six-Times-Faster-Than-Industry-Average-in-Canada/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here for more information.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/0be1ae2f-blog_news-section_18-retailers-grew-six-times-faster_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/0be1ae2f-blog_news-section_18-retailers-grew-six-times-faster_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Klara Roloff</author>            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lightspeed POS Inc. Announces the Acquisition of Gastrofix</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-pos-inc-announces-the-acquisition-of-gastrofix/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/news/lightspeed-pos-inc-announces-the-acquisition-of-gastrofix/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 15:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Klara Roloff]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[Lightspeed POS (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading omnichannel point of sale platform to nearly 57,000 small and medium-sized retail and restaurant locations worldwide, announced in early 2020 that it [&hellip;]]]></description>
                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="628" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/369d101a-blog_news-section_19-acquisition-gastrofix_1200x628.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/369d101a-blog_news-section_19-acquisition-gastrofix_1200x628.jpg" /><p><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2712844-1&amp;h=3879003150&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2F&amp;a=Lightspeed+POS"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed POS</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NYSE: LSPD) (TSX: LSPD), a leading omnichannel point of sale platform to nearly 57,000 small and medium-sized </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2684542-1&amp;h=1709417474&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Fretail%2F&amp;a=retail"><span style="font-weight: 400;">retail</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and </span><a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2684542-1&amp;h=3042123671&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightspeedhq.com%2Fpos%2Frestaurant%2F&amp;a=restaurant"><span style="font-weight: 400;">restaurant</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> locations worldwide, </span><b>announced in early 2020 that it entered into an agreement to acquire Gastrofix</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">, a quickly-growing market leader for cloud-based POS hospitality software in Germany.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed&#8217;s acquisition of Germany&#8217;s premier cloud-based hospitality POS solutions provider brings two high-performing, complimentary teams together to better assist European merchants as they transition to the cloud.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Partnering to serve German hospitality businesses</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With the addition of Gastrofix&#8217;s over 8,000 customer locations, including the Michelin-starred Seven Seas (Hamburg), Leaders Club winner Bar Shuka (Frankfurt) and the luxury Steigenberger Hotels and Resorts, Lightspeed solidifies its presence in Europe, namely in countries such as Germany, Austria and Norway, opening up access to an array of cloud-based services designed to propel European businesses forward. </span></p>
<p><b>With this acquisition, Lightspeed now has the capacity to offer solutions for merchants and restaurateurs in all key regions across Europe.</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This acquisition is timely as German fiscal laws being introduced in 2020 could push merchants and restaurateurs to upgrade to cloud-based POS systems to help them run their businesses and meet new regulatory requirements.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This acquisition builds on Lightspeed&#8217;s growth momentum, having completed a series of acquisitions in 2019, including: Chronogolf, a solution for golf course operators, iKentoo, a Switzerland-based POS solutions provider which serves merchants in over 14 countries across Europe and Africa, and Kounta, a leading Australia-based provider in the hospitality industry.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Combining leadership to look to the future</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;The addition of Gastrofix to our team further solidifies Lightspeed as a leader in cloud-based POS technology and establishes our immense footprint powering SMBs across the globe,&#8221; said Dax Dasilva, Founder and CEO of Lightspeed. &#8220;We are proud to welcome Gastrofix&#8217;s passionate employees to Lightspeed.</span><b> Together, we will create new opportunities for hospitality businesses to reach their highest growth potential amidst shifts in the industry. Lightspeed will continue to execute on further investments to drive complex SMBs forward through the support of top technology in the market.&#8221;</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;Gastrofix and Lightspeed&#8217;s common goal of digitizing the hospitality industry with versatile, efficient cloud-based solutions made the pairing a perfect match,&#8221; said Reinhard Martens, Founder and CEO of Gastrofix. &#8220;We&#8217;re thrilled by the opportunity to combine our resources to reach new customers across Europe.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With the addition of offices in Berlin and Hamburg, Lightspeed&#8217;s footprint now comprises nine European offices including a presence in Amsterdam, Ghent, London, Geneva, Lausanne, Zurich and Paris. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Transaction details</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightspeed has entered into an agreement to acquire all of the outstanding shares of Gastrofix for a base purchase price of approximately US$61 million in cash on closing and the issuance of 1,437,930 subordinate voting shares in the capital of Lightspeed, at a value of US$28.16 per share, subject to post-closing working capital adjustment. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition, certain Gastrofix employees, directly or indirectly, can earn an additional US$4.0 million in deferred cash consideration along with the issuance of 95,464 subordinate voting shares in the capital of Lightspeed, at a value of US$28.16 per share, through January 2022 if various performance objectives are met.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An additional amount of up to US$10.6 million in deferred cash consideration along with the issuance of up to 250,598 subordinate voting shares in the capital of Lightspeed at a value of US$28.16 per share, are payable or issuable to the selling shareholders of the company if revenues overperform the planned revenue from the German market in each of the next 2 years.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For the year ending December 31, 2019, Gastrofix is anticipated to have generated revenue of approximately USD $12.5 million, calculated in accordance with German GAAP and HGB. The company is currently undergoing a conversion to IFRS and anticipates a potential accounting adjustment to reduce revenue by approximately $1.7M for this period to account for certain reseller revenue on a net basis.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://investors.lightspeedhq.com/English/news/news-details/2020/Lightspeed-POS-Inc-Announces-the-Acquisition-of-Gastrofix/default.aspx"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Click here for more information.</span></i></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/369d101a-blog_news-section_19-acquisition-gastrofix_1200x628.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/369d101a-blog_news-section_19-acquisition-gastrofix_1200x628.jpg</image><author>Klara Roloff</author>            </item>
            </channel>
</rss>
