<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
     xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
     xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
     xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
     xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
     xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
    >

    <channel>
        <title>Customers &#8211; Lightspeed POS</title>
        <atom:link href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/feed/?post_type=customers" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com</link>
        <description></description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 17:18:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <sy:updatePeriod>
            hourly        </sy:updatePeriod>
        <sy:updateFrequency>
            1        </sy:updateFrequency>
        
            <item>
                <title>Five Guys</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/five-guys/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/five-guys/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 16:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Meghan O'Neil]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Meghan O'Neil</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>A need for fast answers comes with the territory of operating a quick service restaurant, but Aubert Prévost, president at Koeppel Companies, found himself wasting time and money when his legacy point of sale system would periodically go dark. “Customer service with Oracle MICROS was a big issue for us. We spent countless hours on the phone. The whole system would be down and we couldn’t reboot, so when we faced major issues, we had a tremendous loss of sales.”</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>With Lightspeed’s reliable system and 24/7 support, Prévost said they’ve been able to handle issues as they arise instead of opening support tickets and losing crucial transaction time. “I’m very grateful to have our Lightspeed agent. He’s assigned to us—which is something we would never get with MICROS. When I send him an email, he responds right away.”</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/0d79971a-t11590_fiveguys_halfwidth-1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>69033</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Out There Outfitters</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/out-there-outfitters/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/out-there-outfitters/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 16:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Meghan O'Neil]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Meghan O'Neil</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>Out There Outfitters sells global and accessible brands like Patagonia, The North Face and Yeti. With such popular names, they needed to give their customers a reason to stay loyal to their brick-and-mortar instead of going directly to the supplier. “There’s so much DTC (direct-to-consumer) from our brands,” says McDonald. “All our brands are trying to get their own customers to their own websites because their margins are so much bigger. So if we increase loyalty, our customers won’t go to other places. It keeps them shopping here.”</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Faced with the question of how to increase loyalty at their shop, the owners decided to add Lightspeed Subscriptions to their suite of retail solutions. Under this new model, members of the Out There Outfitters “Insiders Club” receive exclusive access to deals and discounts for one flat fee every month. “We wanted to increase loyalty,” said McDonald. “We have good loyalty but we wanted it to be better. So we thought, “how could we encourage our customers to spend more here and be more connected?’”</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/475317b2-half-width1-min.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>68773</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Gongfu Bao</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/gongfu-bao/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/gongfu-bao/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 15:37:51 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tess Bemporat]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Tess Bemporat</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>With the restaurant landscape changing drastically in the past months, Andrew Bacque, General Manager at Gongfu Bao, was on the lookout for a POS that would not only help them automate and modernize their business, but also steer them safely across the unchartered territory of the COVID-19 pandemic. “When COVID hit, we started taking orders over the phone first, then created a google form which turned out to be a mess,” says Bacque. They needed a POS that would get them over their most urgent hurdles while providing them with improved add-ons and features like more integration options, smoother delivery and an easier setup for online ordering. And Lightspeed fit the bill.</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>By making the switch to Lightspeed and adding Order Ahead and Delivery, Bacque was able to see the results first hand across the restaurant. “Orders are flowing through the FOH even smoother than before—it only takes two minutes for an order to come in instead of 20 minutes prior to Order Ahead. We’ve been able to manage these peak times through the prep-time feature,” says Bacque. For Bacque, it’s all about seeing the results in their bottom line. “Since launching, 17-20% of revenue comes from Order Ahead. We've definitely seen a big return on investment using this tool.”</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/4090ea5d-148487811_1822911707885676_476373287670868092_o-new.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>68618</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>The Marshes</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/the-marshes/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/the-marshes/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 16:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Philip Ednie]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="900" height="495" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/0b6a3112-marshes-thumbnail.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/0b6a3112-marshes-thumbnail.jpg" />]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/0b6a3112-marshes-thumbnail.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/0b6a3112-marshes-thumbnail.jpg</image><author>Philip Ednie</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>It was mid-2017 and Head Golf Professional, Derek MacDonald, wasn’t satisfied with the way his golf course was performing. MacDonald sensed that The Marshes wasn’t getting the full value out of its tee sheet. He didn’t have enough control over tee time pricing and golfers weren’t as loyal as they once were. MacDonald was afraid his course was losing potential revenue and that they were falling behind the competition.</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>The Marshes needed a better solution that would give them full value for their tee sheet and offered multiple payment options. MacDonald settled on Lightspeed Golf; it had a fair distribution policy, didn’t require him to trade tee times, and came with the trappings of a highly advanced and modern all-in-one golf management system. The fully integrated voucher system was also a key determining factor when selecting their new solution.</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/8b77bbbf-marshes-half-width-1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>66931</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Antigonish</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/antigonish/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/antigonish/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 20:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Philip Ednie]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="900" height="495" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/221f0f0a-thumbnail.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/221f0f0a-thumbnail.jpg" />]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/221f0f0a-thumbnail.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/221f0f0a-thumbnail.jpg</image><author>Philip Ednie</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>In 2014, Antigonish Golf & Country Club had gotten into a little bit of a rut. Memberships were stagnant, rounds weren’t growing and the staff was constantly tied up with handling phone bookings in the pro shop. Members and public players weren’t booking online, so senior sales staff were wasting time processing reservations instead of selling pro shop products. Dave Deluzio, Antigonish’s General Manager and Head Golf Professional, had had enough. 
</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Deluzio knew that the legacy software the club was using at the time needed to go. He needed something that was modern, featured advanced marketing tools and could support online bookings through multiple channels. It wasn’t long until he discovered Lightspeed Golf and decided it was worth a shot. He liked its cloud-based features and the fact that the company could build him a brand new website with a sleek and user-friendly online booking tool.</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/4ef82a9f-half-width-1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>66606</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Mystic Pines</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/mystic-pines/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/mystic-pines/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 20:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Philip Ednie]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="900" height="495" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/38f22cf8-thumbnail.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/38f22cf8-thumbnail.jpg" />]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/38f22cf8-thumbnail.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/38f22cf8-thumbnail.jpg</image><author>Philip Ednie</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>To be successful, Mystic Pines would have to find channels that gave them reach into the wider golf market, and they couldn’t afford to have anything but a perfect and seamless experience for those precious first customers. It became clear early on that Lightspeed Golf would be a good fit for the operation given its marketing capabilities and its ability to connect the course to a wider market. </custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Mystic Pines took advantage of Lightspeed Golf’s web agency and built a brand new, optimized website that came complete with a booking engine. The booking engine made it simple for players to book online and interact with the community while simplifying processes in the pro shop. The phone wouldn’t ring constantly, yet through the app, players could see who was playing and if the tee sheet was filling up. </custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/3d68a2a3-half-width-1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>66599</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>The Rise</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/the-rise/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/the-rise/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 19:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Philip Ednie]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="900" height="495" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/38140e6a-thumbnail-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/38140e6a-thumbnail-1.jpg" />]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/38140e6a-thumbnail-1.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/38140e6a-thumbnail-1.jpg</image><author>Philip Ednie</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>In early 2016, Chad Scott was facing a tough challenge. He had recently been hired as the new Director of Golf at a struggling facility. Upon his arrival, Scott could tell his staff wasn’t happy with its current golf management software provider. It wasn’t very user-friendly and, to make things worse, the old system had not been successful in collecting quality data. Scott wanted more out of his software, and its lack of marketing features was not helping the course target or grow its audience in the region.
</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Scott decided to look for a new solution, something that was cloud-based, had progressive marketing features and was user-friendly enough for his staff to understand. It wasn’t long until Scott settled on Lightspeed Golf as his new solution. Since implementing Lightspeed Golf, The Rise has seen a ton of growth. The course is now well established in the region and is continuing to grow year over year. </custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/665a9fa3-half-width-1-1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>66592</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Springfield</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/springfield/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/springfield/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 19:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Philip Ednie]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="900" height="495" src="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/37c32a45-thumbnail.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image wp-stateless-item" alt="" loading="lazy" data-image-size="post-thumbnail" data-stateless-media-bucket="assets.lightspeedhq.com" data-stateless-media-name="img/37c32a45-thumbnail.jpg" />]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    
<enclosure url="https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/37c32a45-thumbnail.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg" />
<image>https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/37c32a45-thumbnail.jpg</image><author>Philip Ednie</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>With their peak season quickly approaching, they needed to build a complete database of customers to facilitate communication. Their old system came with a lot of issues—poor guest communication, subpar database collection and lacklustre email marketing were all holding the golf course back. Every month the team wasted hours in Excel, manually tracking monthly memberships and credit card charges. Clearly, it was time for an update.</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Rich and Morgan had spent 15 years with different tee sheet and point-of-sale systems, so when it came time to pick which provider to go with, the choice was easy. Going with Lightspeed Golf would allow them to greatly improve all aspects of the golf club including communication, marketing, and promotions. Tracking sales data and tailoring messages to different golfer segments was essential to the success that they experienced in the fall and winter of that year.</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/c9315904-half-width-1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>66587</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>KemperSports</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/kempersports/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/kempersports/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 18:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Meghan O'Neil]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Meghan O'Neil</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>Brendan McCarthy is the national director of marketing services at KemperSports. With more than 100 in its managed portfolio, McCarthy needed to know how each facility was performing at a glance but found himself limited with multiple legacy systems. Since many clients utilize different POS systems, McCarthy knew first hand how challenging it was to aggregate data from various sources. This resulted in extra on-site visits and time lost with manual tracking. “We were in the past. We were using very fragmented systems,” said McCarthy. “For properties with Lightspeed’s Analytics for the tee sheet, I'm really able to look at data from an eagle’s eye—hourly analysis, daily analysis and much more—to make better real-time decisions.”</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>In order to target his marketing efforts, McCarthy needed a POS that had the information he needed without adding extra work. When KemperSports adopted Lightspeed, he noticed the business was spending less but getting more. “We were able to reduce costs for a system that allowed us to support our properties from a central location—so in other words, we didn't have to be on-site,” said McCarthy. “I’m also able to look at our pricing tools and say, ‘Okay, this is historically some of my highest priced times. What can I do to influence the rate or improve my capture?”’</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/10/44887966-half-width-1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>65663</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Bahle Farms</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/bahle-farms/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/bahle-farms/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 15:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Philip Ednie]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Philip Ednie</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>Erik Bahle, General Manager, has been working at Bahle Farms since its opening day. Over the years, he has seen his fair share of golf course management systems—some much more intuitive than others. Erik was fed up with expensive systems that offered limited functionalities which didn’t allow him to make smart decisions. “Visibility was definitely one of the main issues we had with our past providers. Their systems provided very little insight into occupancy and customer behaviours which made it very difficult to improve our member experience.”</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Being on the edge of Lake Michigan, Bahle Farms is an isolated facility with very few passersby. Customer relationships are vital to their operation, and given the rapidly evolving global situation, they needed powerful technology that would let them quickly and seamlessly adapt the way they run their business without creating any friction with golfers. Lightspeed Golf’s powerful Tee Sheet was the cornerstone of their flexibility. With tee time intervals customizable to every group and a user-friendly online booking system, they were able to keep golfers safe while running at near maximum capacity. </custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/10/6c9cda1d-bahle-farms_inarticle1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>65536</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Fairways Golf Membership</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/fairways-golf-membership/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/fairways-golf-membership/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 20:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Meghan O'Neil]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Meghan O'Neil</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>Neil McGrew is the director of sales and marketing at Fairways Golf Membership. Before Lightspeed, McGrew was a system manage their courses but saw that it couldn’t keep up. “The pain points for us were the overall financial burden, the speed of transactions, inability to manage multiple facilities' data on an aggregate level to effectively market and the lack of a streamlined booking engine for customers online.”</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Neil knew he needed a POS that could manage four busy golf courses, from the restaurant to the pro shop. Not only did Lightspeed cost 60% less than their previous system, but it allowed Fairways to offer fast and contactless transactions on every facility. “Lightspeed Payments’ new card readers are fast and easy to use—whether the card's inserted or using the tap to pay feature,” said McGrew. “This is a benefit to help us run daily operations more efficiently to keep the experience enjoyable for all.”</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/08/88b11ea8-fairways_inarticle1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>64984</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Kanel</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/kanel/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/kanel/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 19:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Meghan O'Neil]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Meghan O'Neil</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>Kanel was selling products in store and online with Lightspeed’s fully integrated solution. But when a global pandemic temporarily closed her kiosks, she turned her full attention to her digital offerings. In-store, Wiseman leveraged the mobility of Lightspeed's iPad POS to offer personalized service to each customer—complete with tastings and cooking tips—and she wanted to reflect this experience online. With Lightspeed’s easy-to-use eCom solution, built-in blogging tools and the ability to connect her online store to major social media platforms like Facebook, Twitter and Instagram, Wiseman was able to stay true to her brand online. “These tools are our only way to connect with the clientele because they can’t visit us in-store and see or smell the spices.”
</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Kanel co-owner Kim Wiseman knew she needed a POS system that could both work in her physical kiosks and support an online store. She was a veteran in the retail industry and understood the importance of omnichannel, but didn’t think it would be possible with an out-of-the-box solution. “Lightspeed proved me wrong,” says Wiseman. “I tested out the demo and I was blown away by its ease of use and intuitiveness on both retail and eCom platforms.” </custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/06/38387c4d-kanel_visual-4.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>64389</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Le Brow Bar</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/le-brow-bar/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/le-brow-bar/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 00:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tess Bemporat]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Tess Bemporat</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>After trying out different beauty salons in downtown Montreal, Alissa couldn’t find a place that handled eyebrows properly or offered the customer service she was looking for. With the entrepreneurial drive to start something new, she decided to take matters into her own hands and open a unique beauty bar that catered to her needs and offered eyebrow shaping, curated beauty products and great customer service. Alissa followed her passion and created a business that was true to her. “These are traditions from my family that are now almost beauty trends. I see it in the ingredients, in the products, in the influencers that are doing tutorials on YouTube. These things go back to my childhood.”
</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>With no background experience in opening a business, she needed to find a technology partner that would teach her the ropes and be her champion along the way. Lightspeed gave her the ease of use, flexibility and opportunity to grow that she was looking for. “Learning the software, on top of everything else, had to be easy for me. And it really was, it was seamless.” After seeing the benefits reflected directly into her growing business, Alissa took the jump and expanded into eCom and Loyalty to create a smooth omnichannel experience. And it paid. So much so that in her first year with Lightspeed she grew 138%!</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/06/d02d6bdb-brow-bar_7.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>64188</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Editorial</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/editorial/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/editorial/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 17:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tess Bemporat]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Tess Bemporat</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>Before Lightspeed, Editorial was primarily selling products in their brick-and-mortar. Opening an online store was a step Wong wanted to take but with a specific vision and too many ideas, it was put on the shelf. But when a pandemic hit that closed storefronts globally, Wong had to make eCom the priority. "We always wanted to do it with our own templates and we all had different ideas, then everyday life got in the way and it kept getting pushed to the side," says Wong. "And then we were immediately like, "Okay, eCom. Yes. How do we do this?"</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>When Editorial’s doors closed, Wong turned to Lightspeed eCom. With over 50 customizable templates, Wong could create the online shop she envisioned and keep her business operating. She could keep her inventory moving but also stay true to her brand, using technology to offer the personalized experience Editorial became known for. "Just building relationships is a super important thing these days and technology can help with that," says Wong. "Technology is great, as long as you’re able to use it and not go numb to that personal experience."</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/06/5f9e6ae0-editorial_1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>64062</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Tinc Set</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/tinc-set/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/tinc-set/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 16:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tess Bemporat]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Tess Bemporat</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>After having to close Alma, Tinc Set’s full-service sister restaurant focusing on coastal Mediterranean cuisine and natural Catalan wines, Lindsay and Juan went back to the drawing board to figure out their next steps. In spite of the challenges of opening a new restaurant, they decided to jump in with both feet and bring to fruition Tinc Set, an edited version of a project they had long had in the back of their minds. With Lightspeed, they were able to get their new concept up and running in only three weeks. 
</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Lindsay also had to figure out how to design an ordering process that fit their restaurant and the current situation. "We worked really hard to create a website that has an ordering process that’s aesthetically connected." Having used Lightspeed for Alma, they looked to their long-standing technology partner for answers. With Lightspeed, they worked together to find an ordering platform that would work for them and they decided on UEAT. According to Lindsay, "there’s a lot of potential and it has a similar feeling to Lightspeed in the backend."
</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/06/722e6dcd-tinc-set_1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>64046</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Off The Hook</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/off-the-hook/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/off-the-hook/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 15:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tess Bemporat]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Tess Bemporat</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>After outgrowing pen and paper in OTH’s first year, owner Harry Drakopoulos started looking for a system that would help track their inventory and sales without limits. But he kept running into walls while trying out different POS systems. "The last system we used, we noticed right away that their business model just didn't fit our vision," Harry explained. He knew they needed something more: a company that aligned with his vision and offered a POS that would be easy to use and that would actually work for them and not against them.</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>With Lightspeed, OTH found a POS that would grow with them. "Lightspeed was there with us at the very beginning. We felt that their evolution as a company was going to be the same as ours." Lightspeed’s top-notch customer service and ease of use made life easier for Harry, and allowed him to train staff quickly from the get-go. Lightspeed and Off The Hook have been growing and evolving together for the past 11 years.</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/06/96f1e6c1-oth_2.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>64023</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Landscapes Golf Management</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/landscapes-golf-management/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/landscapes-golf-management/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 16:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Étienne Leprette]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Étienne Leprette</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>As COVID-19 started to have a bigger impact across the United States, Scot Wellman, Director of Marketing at Landscapes Golf Management knew his team had to take action. With government legislation permitting the continuation of golf operations in most of their operating regions, certain policies and precautions needed to be introduced to ensure the safety of not only their golfers but their staff as well. Being an MCO with numerous facilities owned or operated by Landscapes Golf Management, they faced the difficult challenge of balancing new government policies as well as new ideas that would help put their golfers and staff at ease while still allowing everyone to enjoy their rounds of golf.</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>One of the first measures Landscapes took was their no-touch policy. They decided to turn on Lightspeed’s online pre-payment function. “We flipped the switch and in seconds, our golfers were able to pay for their rounds online,” says Scot. This allowed the Landscapes Golf Management facilities to close their clubhouses. In an effort to further decrease contact between golfers and employees, the team at Landscapes Golf Management has begun to look into implementing a Self Check-in Kiosk at their courses that would allow their golfers to check-in without speaking to a staff member. Additionally, because they are operating on a cloud-based system, employees are able to work from home. Administrative tasks that can be done remotely are easy to accomplish away from the course with an online solution.
</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/06/c0573d08-landscapes-golf-management_half-width_1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>63945</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Ratcliffe Golf Services</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/ratcliffe-golf-services/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/ratcliffe-golf-services/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 15:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Étienne Leprette]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Étienne Leprette</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>When the cancellations of group bookings and tournaments started to roll in, Del Ratcliffe, Owner and President of Ratcliffe Golf Services knew he had to take action. Del knew he had a duty to do whatever he could to prevent the spread of COVID-19 while keeping his facilities operational. With golf being recognized as an essential service in North Carolina and one of the few activities people can enjoy while still social distancing, Ratcliffe Golf Services wanted to ensure that their golfers and staff were informed of best practices and able to keep themselves safe.</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>One of the first measures that Ratcliffe Golf put in place was the elimination of all cash payments. They immediately turned on the mandatory Online Booking and Pre-Payment functions of Lightspeed’s golf management software. By doing this, one of the critical touch points golfers face when they arrive at a facility—the credit card terminal—was removed. All courses have deployed Lightspeed’s Self Check-In Kiosk where players can check themselves in. In order to ensure that new safety regulations were followed by everyone, Ratcliffe used ChronoPitch Email Marketing to communicate with their database of Charlotte-area golfers. “Having a marketing platform that is synced with our tee sheet database and can trigger multiple communications based on our golfer interactions is great,” says Del, as it allows him to easily pull lists of golfers and send the proper communications to the appropriate people.
</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/06/0cd3e563-ratcliffe_half-width_1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>63939</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Lachute Golf Club</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/lachute-golf-club/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/lachute-golf-club/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 15:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Étienne Leprette]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Étienne Leprette</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>When Benjamin Painchaud stepped into the role of General Manager at Lachute Golf Club in 2017, he knew he wanted to make some changes. Golf had been a part of Benjamin’s life for as long as he could remember, so he had seen first hand what worked and what didn’t at a golf course. With Benjamin’s experience using different software at the various facilities he had worked at over the years, he noticed that “95% of golf courses are running on an archaic system,” and he needed a breath of fresh air for his facility. That’s when Benjamin came across Lightspeed’s golf management software, a modern, user-friendly solution. </custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Having all of the aspects of the course connected to one central system made managing Lachute simpler than ever before. All customer data was now being updated instantaneously in their profiles. He was then able to use this information to cross-reference revenue streams from both his restaurant and golf activities to make his tax filing a simpler task.
ChronoPitch also helped Lacute’s ecommerce grow. Before the season starts, Benjamin sends sales emails to customers informing them of the upcoming season prices. The dynamic list feature helps ensure that the proper customers are getting the intended message.
</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/06/84b2ab9b-lachute_half-width_1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>63933</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Trillium Wood Golf Club</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/trillium-wood/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/trillium-wood/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 15:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Étienne Leprette]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Étienne Leprette</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>Stephen and Kyle, Owner and Sales & Marketing Manager of Trillium Wood Golf Club, had been using a golf management system that was state-of-the-art when the club first opened in 1998. 15 years later, they knew it was time to make a switch. They were tired of being “handcuffed as far as sharing the information and accessing the information." The only way they could check their tee sheet or customer database was in the office at the pro shop, and that just wasn’t cutting it for them. They needed a cloud-based solution that would allow them to access information from their two other courses from anywhere and at any time. They also wanted a solution that would allow them to use the data gathered from their tee sheet to better market their courses. </custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Trillium Wood felt that Lightspeed’s modular capability closely aligned with the direction in which they were going. They realized that they could further improve with the different add-ons and integrations available to them; they were able to add additional features as they needed them. Their custom branded website allowed their golfers to purchase memberships and packages online while the information automatically flows into the system without any additional work from staff. They also opted to add ChronoPitch to their arsenal. Now, they can segment customers into lists and craft email campaigns to bring back more golfers. Additionally, their custom-branded mobile app allows golfers to book tee times anywhere.</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/06/7f0c9b7d-trillium-wood_half-width_1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>63927</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Wellington National Golf Club</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/wellington-national/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/wellington-national/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 15:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Étienne Leprette]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Étienne Leprette</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>In 2016 Ted Strelec, Director of Golf and General Manager at Wellington National Golf Course, was tasked with finding a new management system. Leadership and management at the private Palm Beach, Florida-based golf course had grown frustrated with the lack of integrations and inefficiencies caused by their dated legacy software. The club decided that it was finally time to update from its old system and find a new club management software. Ted knew he had to find a software platform that could integrate with both food and beverage and pro shop points of sale.</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Ted found Lightspeed and was impressed by its robust integration capabilities, high quality design and fair value for price. Within two days, the course was fully live and operating on Lightspeed. Now, members find it much easier to get information regarding tee times, member directories or course-related announcements. With accounting, retail and restaurant house accounts all consolidated into one statement, members can monitor their accounts in one easy-to-access report. In addition, selling gift cards, tracking the tournament prize fund and monitoring inventory is much more efficient. Team members in the pro shop love how user-friendly and helpful the software is in their day-to-day operations.</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/06/9fa2a692-wellington-national-_half-width_1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>63920</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Antognolla Golf Course</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/antognolla-golf-course/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/antognolla-golf-course/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Étienne Leprette]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Étienne Leprette</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>Keith Haslam, Managing Director at Braemar Golf, provides management consulting to golf course developers from early planning and design to post-execution. One of the specific requirements that Haslam had been tasked with for Antognolla Golf Course was to ensure rounds could be booked online. Initially, the website designers opted to look at generic room booking software. This search turned up lackluster results, and Keith knew that he wanted to give his client a solution that would grow as the resort did. He needed something that was aligned with the future of the golf industry.</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Antognolla had been using spreadsheets to manage members, tee sheets, accounting and bookings. It was clear that better technology was essential to improve inefficient processes, improve service levels and understand the business with better data analysis. Lightspeed’s golf management software stood out as a top contender for Antognolla. The company’s best-of-breed approach meant the golf course could freely add features and functions to implement a better strategy without imposing too many changes at once. With training sessions on Lightspeed, staff onboarding went smoothly. </custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/06/a9009163-antognolla_half-width_1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>63913</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Jackson National</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/jackson-national/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/jackson-national/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 14:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Étienne Leprette]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Étienne Leprette</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>Another season had passed at Jackson National's two properties, and Dana Talkington, General Manager, was getting tired of wasting time managing her business between an old POS, Microsoft Office, and a pen and paper tee sheet. To make things worse, the company that provided them with POS software had recently been acquired, and customer support service levels had dropped off. It took days to get critical questions answered, and the system itself was getting clunky and hard to work with.</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Jackson National needed a system that could manage all the parts of the operation from one simple platform. Data needed to flow seamlessly from one tool to the next to ensure recording customer information and storing data from the tee sheet was user-friendly and straightforward. That's when Dana discovered Lightspeed. As an operation that managed tee time bookings through pen and paper, the cloud-based tee sheet offered many benefits. In addition, they were able to migrate their pro shop and food and beverage operations to Lightspeed, giving them a fully integrated solution. Implementation was quick and easy, and the team at Jackson National was impressed by the speed and ease of interacting with Lightspeed's 24/7 support team.</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/06/e234bb21-jackson-national_half-width_1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>63902</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Sargent Steam Cleaners</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/sargent-steam-cleaners/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/sargent-steam-cleaners/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 20:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Alix Fraser</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>When Sargent Steam opened their doors, they quickly found their original POS system to be unreliable. “I spent lots of time on the phone with the help desk,” Julie says; she was spending far too much time in the help centre trying to manage the fiddly system. That’s when Julie discovered Lightspeed OnSite, the POS system that preceded Lightspeed Retail. It was intuitive to use, with everyday retail tasks easy to find in the system. </custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>While the ease-of-use made OnSite a superstar system for Sargent Steam, being tethered to a physical server eventually started to take its toll. As the hardware aged, the server didn’t feel as reliable—and Julie and her team were unable to work anywhere but in the store, which made trying to operate their unintegrated ecommerce platform a pain. Lightspeed Retail presented Sargent Steam with an opportunity to stick with their trusted POS provider while upgrading to cloud-based tools.</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/05/fdc119ae-sargent-steam_inarticle1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>63459</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Via Ciclante</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/via-ciclante/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/via-ciclante/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alix Fraser]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Alix Fraser</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>While their bicycle repairs were classified as essential services under Ontario’s legislative efforts to contain the spread of COVID-19, Via Ciclante still needed a way to keep their employees and their customers safe. “In the past, people came to the store, which meant we spent time with the client to get that job done. But we can’t do that with social distancing,” says operations manager Jean-Paul Tesolin.</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Already interested in the efficiency online scheduling could give their business before the COVID-19 pandemic, Via Ciclante took the opportunity to use <a target="_blank" href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/integrations/booxi/">booxi integrated with Lightspeed</a> to help them continue to provide repairs without the risk of generating crowds and endangering their staff and customers. “We’ve created a schedule on booxi so every 10 minutes you can drop off a bike,” explains Tesolin. “So on booxi, the customer can plan their time, drop off their bike and we will collect it at the door and then send a message about their repairs through Lightspeed.”</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://stg-assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2020/04/419de931-viaciclante-challenge.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>62990</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>CBD Plus USA</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/cbd-plus-usa/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/cbd-plus-usa/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 22:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Meghan O'Neil]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Meghan O'Neil</author><custom_modules_master_1_description>In a hyper-competitive market, CBD Plus USA wanted a POS with scalable technology that would help them keep pace with one of the fastest-growing industries around. A modern cloud-based platform, advanced analytics and fast payments were necessities to grow the business. “Honestly, one of the best features is that I can just log in anywhere and I can view all of my stores right there. It's very easy for me to help one of my stores remotely and figure out a problem,” says Stone. After seeing its capabilities in a past venture, CEO Ryan Vicedomini decided to launch CBD Plus USA with Lightspeed.</custom_modules_master_1_description>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Danielle B</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/danielle-b/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/danielle-b/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 21:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elina Barklon]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Elina Barklon</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>Operations Manager Ariel Bruck was faced with the best problem a retailer can have—a busy store. Ariel had begun recruiting outside of the family to help him with the additional work but he also needed a POS that could keep up. With more customers than ever, Ariel wanted to make sure they were still being well taken care of. He was looking to simplify training so his new employees could focus on the customers instead of trying to understand a complex system. </custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Lightspeed’s sleek and modern interface was the tool Ariel needed to set his team up for success. With an easy-to-use interface and advanced features like inventory management and detailed customer profiles, employees could spend more time offering the boutique’s trademark personalized service. Ariel was impressed with the functionality and design of Lightspeed and could continue building lifelong relationships with his customers. </custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2019/12/871a2dd5-danielle-b_inarticle1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>61428</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Cricket Newman</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/cricket-newman/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/cricket-newman/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 17:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elina Barklon]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Elina Barklon</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>Cricket wanted her retail store to feel collaborative and inviting—a true extension of her event planning company. It was important that her employees and customers connected beyond the transaction of a salem but getting the tools to revamp a traditional retail concept was a challenge. “Nobody in my shop's allowed to stand behind the counter unless they're actually ringing somebody up. It's greeting, it's listening. It's a very traditional customer service approach,” says Cricket.</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Lightspeed’s retail solution was recommended to Cricket by a fellow business owner. Its cloud-based system could be used on the sales floor where employees were personally connecting with each customer. Cricket’s team became ideal brand ambassadors, embodying her people-first mission. “We can run it remotely on an iPad, which we love. Everything about it is just very user-friendly.”</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2019/11/72644eba-cricket-newman_inarticle1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>61396</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>The Regency Club</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/the-regency-club/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/the-regency-club/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 14:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Joe Jarvis]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Joe Jarvis</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>Before using Lightspeed, Rahul was spending a lot of time and money training his staff and maintaining The Regency Club. Although evenings were often busy, he wasn’t making enough from the day trade to justify his investments. He lacked the proximity to the city, so missed out on the bustling lunch trade near large offices. The Regency Club had its loyal regulars, but Rahul knew that wasn’t enough. He’d have to attract a broader customer base if the business was to survive.</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Since adopting Lightspeed, Rahul has made smart changes to his business. Its ‘plug and play’ style integrations like Lightspeed delivery have enabled him to set up a takeaway service quickly and easily. He used the special menu function to introduce a lunchtime co-working space, drawing in local workers and freelancers with a cheaper menu. He was also pleasantly surprised to find that with Lightspeed’s easy-to-use platform, he could cut staff training time down from six weeks to just two! With increased revenue and extra time, he’s now able to focus on growing his business. “Lightspeed really gives a business all the tools and support they need to improve and grow”.</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2019/11/a00a6d7e-regency-700x375-1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>61259</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
                    <item>
                <title>Fleurty Girl</title>
                <link>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/fleurty-girl/</link>
                <comments>https://www.lightspeedhq.com/customers/fleurty-girl/#respond</comments>
                <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 21:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
                <dc:creator><![CDATA[Elina Barklon]]></dc:creator>
                
                                    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>

                                                                <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
                                                                                    <author>Elina Barklon</author><custom_modules_master_0_description>Making the leap from in-home business to a full-fledged retail operation would be impossible without the right tools. Without a cloud-based POS, managing one location’s inventory would be time-consuming enough--if Fleurty Girl was ever going to grow into multiple locations, Lauren needed a system that could streamline her business and free her up to keep focusing on expanding.</custom_modules_master_0_description>
<custom_modules_master_1_description>Lightspeed enabled Fleurty Girl to make the leap and embrace Lauren Haydel’s retail dreams of expansion. “Lightspeed allowed me to move at the speed of light,” she shares. “We grew fast and it allowed me to do so by properly getting the multi-store inventory set up. We have our eCom shop under the same platform, so the girls in the store could see if the website had any stock available as well. It just allowed us to flourish.” Recently, Fleurty Girl expanded into airport retail, aided by Lightspeed’s easily scalable POS.</custom_modules_master_1_description>
<featured_image> https://assets.lightspeedhq.com/img/2019/11/e210626c-fleurty-girl_inarticle1.jpg</featured_image>
<custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>61226</custom_modules_master_0_featured_image>
            </item>
            </channel>
</rss>
